She looks just like you!
Why?
Why is she a kid?
Tenth File
Trap in Azabu
Ruriko-sama.
The centipede is programmed
to not harm the girl.
Ryouko-san used that
to her advantage.
So she used the girl
as a shield and escaped.
I’ll go after them.
There is no need.
Ruriko-sama?
It’s also amusing to test out
the power he mentioned.
They’re not coming after us.
So it seems.
We’re okay now.
Hey, hang in there!
Superintendent,
you know, don’t you?
Please tell me.
Who exactly is she?
I’ll tell you later.
Nonagase-kun,
head for my house.
Understood.
Who exactly is she?
Who do you think?
I’m the one asking
the questions.
Then I’ll answer first.
Even though
it’s a childish idea,
my first thought was
that she was a clone.
A SF-type theory.
But that’s impossible since the technology behind cloning isn’t that advanced yet.
Next, I thought she might
be your illegitimate child.
But I shrugged
that off right away.
Of course.
That would leave
only one possibility,
that she is your sister.
Continue.
I hear that your father,
Mr. Yakushiji Hiroki, is a ladies man.
Even though he’s already sixty,
he still keeps numerous mistresses.
Although he’s in
New York right now.
Who did you hear that from?
You told me some time ago.
Huh? Did I?
Something about having different mistresses from Monday to Friday.
I see.
You’ve come to the conclusion that she’s someone whom my father produced, eh?
Perhaps this was due to grudges against JACES or maybe it was for money.
Either way,
someone confined her.
And after you found out, you rescued her and took her into protective custody.
So, what’s the real story?
Mistress.
What’s wrong?
Terrible.
Is it fun?
Boring.
So you can talk.
What’s your name?
I don’t know.
We’re in the middle of a program, but breaking news has just arrived.
Just now, there was an explosion at DK Pharmaceutical’s office-and-storage areas in Toyosu.
Destroying evidence is fine and dandy, but that’s going too far, Ruriko-san.
We’ve just received more news.
It appears there was another
explosion two minutes ago.
I repeat.
Just now, there was an explosion at DK Pharmaceutical’s office-and-storage areas in Toyosu.
You have an
interesting hobby.
Oh, those.
And we have reports that
there was a second explosion as well.
They’re gods,
to protect me from fire.
Back when I worked
for the Defense Agency,
The police are investigating whether this explosion is due to the first explosion or a terrorist attack.
there was a mysterious legend concerning a nearby lake.
The Azabu Toad Lake Legend, right?
These are images of the scene.
So you know.
There’s smoke rising
from multiple locations.
I read about it in a book
by Okamoto Kidou.
It conveys the magnitude
of the explosion to us.
Regarding “that”.
I’ve talked to
the mayor about it.
All that’s left is…
I know.
Just like how the Metropolitan Police Department and JACES have strong ties,
the ties between NPP and the Ministry of Defense are also rock solid.
I feel relieved to hear that from you,
the one who is essentially the owner of NPP.
As previously promised,
once we complete all the tasks,
I will present you
the Prime Minister’s seat.
But still, you lay down
your plans really carefully.
To think that you’d go this far
just to erase one person.
That woman,
Yakushiji Ryouko, is worthy of it.
I ended up staying at
Yakushiji Ryouko’s house.
In the end, she didn’t say
a word about the girl.
Judging from her mannerisms,
she’ll probably never reveal the truth.
Superintendent, is that you?
You’re…
You need to sleep soon or else you won’t be able to wake up tomorrow morning.
I’m not sleepy yet.
Close your eyes and
try counting sheep.
If I do that, can I sleep?
Yes.
One sheep.
Two sheep.
Three sheep.
Four sheep.
Five sheep.
Six sheep.
Seven sheep.
Fifteen sheep…
Sixteen… shee…
Guess I have no choice.
Hey, Izumida.
Izumida.
Pot.
Finished.
You made this?
That’s…!
“100 Infallible Cooking
Techniques For New Wives”
Oh, that.
It belongs to
Marianne and Lucienne.
Right?
But it’s a Japanese book…
Stop worrying
about the details.
Izumida.
Delicious!
Which clothes
do you want, mon ami?
Please don’t be modest.
Choose what
you like, mon ami.
So you decided to
call her Monami-chan?
That’s what the two call her.
Izumida-kun, I wouldn’t count on your French skills to begin with, but…
… haven’t you at least
read Agatha Christie?
Monami isn’t a name.
It means “my trusted friend” in French.
Poirot often used it when he called Hastings, his best friend.
But I guess it works.
Huh?
She needs a name anyway.
Starting today,
your name is Monami.
Monami?
Izumida-kun chose the name,
so no complaints, okay?
Do I look good in it?
If you don’t work,
you don’t eat.
Monami, that’s what
you will be wearing.
You look good in it.
I see.
So you don’t remember
a thing before you woke up.
Yes, Mistress.
Izumida-kun…
… said you’re my sister.
Sister?
It means a different child
born from the same parent.
Parent?
Listen…
Oh yeah, you wouldn’t know.
I’m sorry.
Superintendent.
Hand me my bathrobe.
I brought what
you requested.
What is that?
Her reward.
Since you look like me,
it looks good on you.
Yes, Mistress.
No.
In a situation like this…
Merci.
Good work.
How many times
do I have to explain?
We don’t know where
they went either.
Superintendent!
Izumida-san!
Are you watching this?
What have you been
doing this past week?
Please hurry and come back!
When do you plan
to go back to work?
When I feel like it.
I see. So she’s
called Monami-chan.
It’s a pretty name.
I wonder how it’s written.
Mofuku is Japanese for funeral wear.
Mo as in mofuku.
Namuamidabutsu is a buddhist prayer.
Na as in namuamidabutsu.
The kanji for beautiful
can also be read as mi.
And beautiful…
More importantly,
what about my question?
Please give me
a bit more time.
Please hurry up!
I can’t let her stay
here much longer.
Yes, that’s right.
That’s why we have no choice but to raise her somewhere far away
where they won’t get her,
even if it’s in Africa or South America.
Monami disappeared?
She wasn’t on
the rooftop either.
That means…
Hello. Nonagase-kun?
Understood.
I’ll send the
information to you.
She’s headed to Azabu.
How do you
know her location?
Move!
Yakushiji-san, we would
like to speak with you.
Oh, shut up!
Please, no violence.
Superintendent,
who are they?
Probably former
self defense forces.
They’re dogs for NPP now.
You can pay me next time.
Thank you.
This is NPP SP-5,
R-9 has arrived at
the scene as planned.
Yakushiji-san, we would
like to speak with you.
She’s stopped moving.
This is the police.
Please hurry.
Monami-chan!
Izumida.
Izumida!
Run!
Quickly!
Stop!
R-9 retrieval, complete.
We will now head back.
I’m terribly sorry.
I was with her,
yet it turned out like this…
It’s not your fault.
And the monster you saw is probably the toad that appears in the Azabu legends.
A toad?
Toad and centipede?
Is this an old ninja
movie or something?
Maybe she has the
same power you do.
What do you mean?
You have the power to attract things not from this world.
Who said that?
Nonagase-san.
I hated myself
for being powerless.
Good work.
Thank you.
The late Tatsumi-sensei will transform you from a larva into a butterfly.
For now, sleep well.
Calmly.
One sheep…
Two sheep…
The people and events in this work are purely fictional.
Any resemblance to existing people or events is entirely coincidental.
Here’s a riddle.
Bring it on.
What’s a sweet
version of me?
Dorayaki is red bean paste sandwiched in between two small pancakes.
Dorayaki Oryou.
What if I drove?
Drive Oryou.
Then what if I’m in a world
of swords and magic—
Yakushiji Ryouko’s Supernatural Case File,
File Number 09-C: The Princess of Takanawa.
Please look forward to it.
Then the future—