It's strange.
When I'm with you, I get the feeling that a crisis of this level is nothing.
You're right.
I'll stop a tank with the wink of an eye.
You really did stop it!
What?
Ciao.
I see now.
Now the players are all set.
Commence advance!
Head for Shiba!
Target has seized a tank and breached the siege.
She's headed straight here.
Fire!
Superintendent, it's dangerous. Please come inside.
Full speed ahead!
What's that?
A souvenir from France that my cute maids brought back.
Oh, the perfume you mentioned the other day.
Hold on to this.
B-But...
I understand.
They're here.
Where are you looking?
Yakushiji Ryoko!
What?
Really. Where are you looking?
It seems that no one is here.
They just left.
Report from Akasaka District Group.
We will assemble at JACES's main office momentarily.
We will enter in 60 minutes as planned.
What?!
To think that SDF would support NPP this much...
Didn't you know?
Disregarding the higher officials,
most of the soldiers participating in the practice are being controlled by Ruriko's tainted radio waves.
Wherever we go, there are soldiers waiting.
Is this really Tokyo?
I'm hungry.
I wonder what will happen to us.
Wait there, you evil villains.
You really take your time.
Or perhaps you were waiting for me?
My, you really don't learn.
Izumida-kun, let's go.
Y-Yes.
W-Well done.
Y-Yeah,
well done.
That's our superintendent!
You're really cool.
Wonderful.
I've found them!
I'm disappointed in you.
What do you mean by that?
I had thought that you would have played your pieces more wisely.
I don't care how I play my pieces.
The winner prevails.
All I have to do is not lose.
You think you can win in this situation?
Izumida!
Monami-chan.
Please.
Please, come with me.
Please!
Izumida, come with me!
Come to my side!
I can't do that.
How come?
Because I'm not human?
No!
Definitely not!
Then why?
You come to my side.
You shouldn't be with these people!
Ruriko-san, you're mistaken!
I wasn't planning to stick my nose into the conflict between you and the Yakushiji family,
but Monami's...
Have you ever considered Monami's feelings?
Monami has a heart and is living to her fullest!
No matter what people say, she is a human being!
Rather, you're the one who's lower than human.
You wouldn't hesitate to sacrifice a person's heart or life for your own objectives!
Izumida...
Mistress.
You talk big when you need to, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I said more than I should have...
For your reward, I'll let you in on a little secret.
S-Something so outrageous?
Oh, you think so too?
Of course I do!
Have you finished bidding your farewells?
In that case, I'll make you take your exit.
It might be you who makes an exit.
Looks like it's here.
Direct hit!
Run away!
Your unpredictability leaves me speechless.
You're still talking.
To the truck.
Izumida.
Nonagase, I'm going.
I don't want to be crushed.
Geez.
I've decided that...
I'll crush the Shiba that you reign over as Queen.
Aren't you scared of dying?
Winning is more important.
It's not over yet!
She's amazing.
She's starting to look like Oryo-sama.
She probably lost sight of herself due to the extreme tension.
The attack stopped?
Seems so.
Foolish humans, bow before me!
Superintendent!
Wh-What happened to Izumida?
Izumida!
He laid on top of you to cover you.
He probably tried to protect you.
Are you interested in teaming up with me?
What?
JACES is the only thing you can get your hands on, even if you go with Ruriko, right?
But if we work together, we can rule this country...
No, the whole world.
Are you serious?
I always am.
If there are two Yakushiji Ryokos, nothing's impossible.
Two Yakushiji Ryokos?
You are me.
And I am you.
From our face to the way we think, we're exactly the same.
And our taste in men too.
But there's one thing different.
If I were you, I would have defeated my hateful rival in love, without the help of anyone.
Come to my place, Monami.
And go after my life diligently.
Don't you think a life like that would be thrilling and fun?
M-Mistress.
Izumida!
Hey.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm glad.
Run!
Are you okay?
Yes I am, Mistress.
It's not over yet.
Don't!
Ryoko-san...
Your existence is unforgivable.
Izumida-san, please don't hate me.
I enjoyed talking to you.
Hold on there.
Izumida-kun!
What?
What's this?
Superintendent, that's...
Show me.
I want to see.
Th-This is...?
N-No!
Created one and creator,
if one does not seek to melt,
keep the secret.
What is...?
[Note: Senjuushou is a collection of fairy tales and legends that is attributed to Saigyou Houshi.]
A verse from the Senjuushou written by Saigyou Houshi.
Saigyou Houshi made a mistake when he tested the secret arts of Hangon.
It was because he burned a certain kind of incense that wasn't supposed to be burnt.
Then, is that perfume...?
I had the JACES laboratory in Paris make it with the ingredient extracted from the aromatic tree as its base.
But to think that Nonagase Kazuma was also created with the Hangon technique...
Yes, he probably didn't know it either.
Ryoko-san.
Play with me again someday.
Who created Isurugi Ruriko?
Most likely the real Ruriko.
Whether the original is alive or dead is unknown.
But even created people have the ability to use the secret arts of Hangon.
Ruriko, created from the original, applied the same method to create more copies of herself.
That's how it is.
This isn't over yet.
I'm sure a different Ruriko will come before us.
Which means the fight between the Yakushiji family and Isurugi Ruriko will continue?
I would think so.
For some reason, in the face of a supernatural existence that threatens the Yakushiji family,
Yakushiji Ryoko looked like she was enjoying herself.
Yakushiji Ryoko's violence was reported as an unfortunate accident during the practice.
I'm sure my boss, who has a talent for deception, did the spadework behind the scenes.
Holy night.
It is the calm before a storm.
Various rumors have been mentioned in the media: that I am resigning from duty,
or that I will officially assume the office of president of JACES,
or that I am getting engaged.
None of it is true.
What? That's different from what I heard.
I intend to continue my job with the same sincere heart...
No, with an even more sincere heart.
Media personnel who have gathered here,
This is terrible!
the bosses I love and respect,
and the citizens of Japan, please give me warm, yet strict guidance.
Ryoko-chan, you're really good at lying.
I'm ready.
Oh my.
It looks wonderful on you.
Izumida-kun, hurry up and apply the suntan lotion.
I came with you since I was told that we have work.
Of course we do.
What kind of work?
To dig up the people who bashed me.
We need to clean them up after the New Year arrives...
Izumida, let's swim.
N-No, I'll decline the offer.
Let's swim!
Let's go!
Come on.
I can't.
She just gave me some work.
What are you doing?
Come on, take it off!
Get changed. Get changed.
H-Hey, wait!
H-Help me!
What?
What are you doing, Izumida-kun?
I-I'm sorry, Superintendent.
You must stay close by.
I'm sorry.
That's not it.
Yes, I'll accompany you.
Well done.
My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.
Thirty-three years old.
I am Yakushiji Ryoko's...
You've heard about it, haven't you?
About corpses that still move, even after they die,
that execrate the living.
This is what you call the killers who hunt the immortal corpses:
Shikabane Hime.