Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
There was another suicide last night?
At the suicide apartment complex, eh?
How many does that make?
Five.
Here you go.  Here's your share.
As usual, there's a lot of work to do today.
Being Yakushiji Ryoko's subordinates,
we receive various information about supernatural cases.
It is also part of our job to investigate them.
I like this one.
"I know the culprit of the serial suicide case."
"They are all caused by an Ultrasound Bug."
"An Ultrasound Bug?"
He should have drawn a picture for us.
I suspect it's something like this!
Here you go, the Ultrasound Bug.
And the one who sent this goes by the name "Mushimushi-kun."
This isn't something we should do first thing in the morning...
All-nighters aren't good for you, Oryo.
I'm just bored of everyday life.
Oh my, if that's the case, apply for a transfer.
What are you doing on my floor?
It doesn't belong to you.
It does.
Hey!
Fine.
It's no use arguing over useless matters so early in the morning.
Anyway, have you heard about Takamoto Ayaka?
Oh, that bookworm.
I heard she jumped off last night.
I wonder if someone broke her heart.
Your classmate just died and that's all you have to say?
No!
Anyone who commits suicide is stupid, regardless of the reason.
It was stupid to have consulted you.
What is it?
Do you intend to investigate this case?
She's not someone who'd commit suicide.
This also happened at the suicide apartment complex too.
Something about that bothers me.
It's outside my jurisdiction.
Then stay out of it!
Superintendent, let's turn on our patrol lights at least.
I don't have something that ugly on this car.
This is Midorikawa-san's thesis and the list of students during the time he was in school.
Thank you.
Midorikawa Shuuji was one of those who jumped from the suicide apartment complex.
He graduated from university with excellent grades
and then worked for Tama Acoustic Research Laboratory.
It is a prestigious company within its field often sought out by the police for help in areas such as voiceprint identification.
According to the local police files,
he was highly trusted and it didn't look like he had any troubles.
Azuma-sensei, thank you for your hard work.
Matsumura-kun, I told you to feed the insects.
You haven't, have you?
I'm sorry.  I was just about to.
They will die.
They may be just insects to you,
but to me, they're valuable experimental organisms.
I'm very sorry.
They'll die.
Oh, I'm sorry.
He's... a lecturer.
Does he keep insects?
Yes, for ultrasound research.
Did you find out?
Yes.
It looks like Midorikawa-san had a very close friend.
A classmate?
What's his name?
Gotcha.
This is a species of cricket from the Mogoplistidae  family.
What you hear now is the sound it usually makes with its wings.
But actually, there are more sounds.
Using this device...
What is that?
Oh, this is a...
A bat detector, right?
Y-Yes.
A bat...
A bat detector.
It's a device that converts bats' ultrasonic frequencies into audible ones.
You're quite knowledgeable.
I just happen to know.
It sounds like Morse code.
This is the ultrasound the Mogoplistidae  is making.
"Ultrasound?"
As expected from Mushimushi-kun.
That's you, right?
Mushimushi-kun.
Midorikawa and I researched a lot together while in school.
There was a friendly competition between us.
So you're something like rivals.
Something like that.
Although I lost to him.
Lost?
He worked for a top-notch acoustic research laboratory while I'm a petty lecturer.
Will you tell us about the Ultrasound Bug?
Okay.
You're aware of the effects that ultrasound waves have on the body, right?
Sounds that we find unpleasant contain frequencies we cannot hear.
Midorikawa and I wondered whether insects that emit those frequencies existed.
So that's the Ultrasound Bug.
Did you find any?
It'll be the discovery of the century if we did.
Oh, how long we searched for them!
We recorded the sounds of as many leaf beetles as we could!
But in the end, we couldn't find any.
Later, he found it, in secret.
But he failed.
He became a victim of the Ultrasound Bug during his research.
Poor guy.
He went for the wool and came home sheared instead.
So you're saying the suicides are caused by the ultrasound waves that bug emits?
They definitely are.
It sends a stimulus of some sort to the cerebral nerve,
and that stripped Midorikawa and the others of their rationality.
What makes you so sure?
I'm an ultrasound specialist.
Then is that insect still somewhere in the apartment complex?
Yes, it is.
It's hiding.
If you leave it alone, there will be more casualties.
I'm positive.
He's just some radio wave geek.
Yes, he is.
His stories are contradicting too.
Contradicting?
Well, because if what he said was true,
Midorikawa should have been the first victim.
Midorikawa only jumped last week.
Azuma-sensei was looking for the Ultrasound Bug with Midorikawa Shuuji, right?
Yes, that's what he said.
And he found it, right?
According to Azuma-sensei.
Yes, but that's a delusion.
Even if it is, Azuma-sensei still believes Midorikawa did, right?
Then I wonder why he doesn't want that insect.
He said that it may still be in the apartment complex, right?
Yet, he didn't ask us to capture it at all.
Maybe because he's saying this knowing it's delusional?
It seems you're starting to be delusional yourself.
All thanks to you.
Fix it.
You were talking with your friend on the phone when you suddenly felt strange, and...?
What do you mean by feeling strange?
I thought my friend, laughing on the other end, was laughing at me.
Then I started to feel really miserable.
I kept recalling bad memories.
And you tried to commit suicide?
Yes.
How about now?
I'm all right now, thanks to you.
Is that so?
I'm glad.
What exactly was it?
You were possessed by the Ultrasound Bug.
A cell phone, eh?
I see.
Well then, let's all work hard and look for the Ultrasound Bug.
Yeah!
Roger, we will begin our search.
Everyone, this is what I think the Ultrasound Bug looks like, so please look for something like this.
Umm, Yakushiji-san.
Yes, Sensei?
There was another suicide attempt yesterday, right?
Don't you need the residents to evacuate?
And I think the investigation team is rather small.
Umm, it's hard to bring this up to you, but...
Even if I said that the Ultrasound Bug is here, people would only mock me.
And the best I could do was to persuade my subordinates.
That's why I've even asked you to come along, even though I know that you're busy.
Well then, let's quickly get this started.
Quickly.
Yes, quickly.
We don't want to waste any time.
Quickly.
You're ending the investigation?
Impossible!
The Ultrasound Bug is definitely here!
You ought to expand your investigation team, Yakushiji-san!
There is no need to.
Okay, investigation complete.
Everyone retreat.
Yakushiji-san!
H-Hey!
Later that night, Azuma Katsuhiko called us, claiming to have captured the Ultrasound Bug.
And where he captured it was...
...in the room of Midorikawa Shuuji, the man who committed suicide.
That Oryo, calling me out here.
She found the culprit?
So she is  investigating this case.
It's Oryo.
Yes, I'm already there.
Fast?
Of course I am!
Unlike someone I know, I go to places 30 minutes in advance.
Hello?
Oyuki?
Is something wrong?
Hello?
Hello?!
You hate me, don't you?
Shoot me.
What are you saying?
Living proudly isn't the only thing you need to do.
You've never even had a lover!
I have!
Liar!
You've been alone all along.
You have nothing.
You're empty.
That's not true...
You're different from me.
Poor girl.
I...
I have everything.
In the end, I'm...
It's somewhere here!
Look for it!
So this is...
The Ultrasound Bug.
It doesn't have any wings, but it looks like a species of Homoeogryllus japonicus .
It's... ew...
"Ew?"
Oh, okay...
It means disgusting.
"Ew!"
What sound...
It sounds like a cell phone vibrating.
So the ultrasound waves that make people go insane are mixed in with this sound.
My subordinates should have captured the Ultrasound Bug by now.
I see.
So I walked right into your trap.
Too bad you couldn't kill me.
The radio wave the Ultrasound Bug emits is at the same frequency as cell phone signals.
That's right, 1.5 GHz.
The ultrasound enters the cell phone conversation,
lowers the caller's self-esteem, and heightens feelings of solitude.
Eventually causing the caller to commit suicide.
Wonderful analysis.
That's exactly what happens.
To begin with, I acquired that insect from an enthusiast I met on the net.
That's why I don't know much about its classification, let alone its habitat.
But I'm the one who discovered its relation to cell phones.
It's always me who makes the discoveries.
Not Midorikawa.
If you wrote and published a paper on that, you would be famous.
Yet you killed Midorikawa.
He was always stealing from me.
My ideas, and even my discoveries.
He would always write papers, publish, and make it his work!
And everyone respected him, even though I'm the one who really deserves it!
What low self-esteem.
That's why you informed me via e-mail.
You wouldn't understand the hardship I've gone through.
I don't.
I don't even want to.
You made Midorikawa commit suicide
and you tried to cover it up by using that bug on innocents.
It was also part of an experiment.
"An experiment?"
Experiment, eh?
That's a subtly deceptive argument scientists often make.
Some superficial justice.
Do you hate me that much?
But don't worry.
I hate you too.
Is that so?
Thanks.  I'm relieved.
Well then, what are you going to do?
Will you arrest me?
Yes, that would be the case.
I've got evidence and testimony too.
I'm sure everyone will believe me now.
Oh, what to do now?
I've still got an important job: to reveal the experimental results to the entire world.
Why don't you do it through your cell?
What is this?
Yakushiji-san, that wasn't the only insect.
So what?
I can't hear your phone.
Seems like you've really gone insane.
Resonance?
Just joking.
I don't have anything to worry about.
Too bad!
Superintendent!
Izumida-kun!
Superintendent.
Superintendent!
Yakushiji Ryoko!
Azuma!
Let's go.
Superintendent!
Are you okay?
Superintendent, are you hurt?
Izumida!
Yes?
You called me by my name, didn't you?
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
It was an emergency.
Even in emergencies, do you call your boss by her name?
No, umm... I'm sorry.
Look forward to your bonus.
What were those tears she showed earlier?
Her reason for jumping?
No.  Yakushiji Ryoko shouldn't have anything to worry about.
She toyed with me again at that moment.
Dreadful Yakushiji Ryoko.
An all-nighter again, Oryo?
Unlike you, I'm a busy person.
And?  What did you do after?
Yeah.
And...
That's right.
She was very noisy and...
Your older sister is your only sibling, right?
Probably.
Probably?
My father keeps many mistresses.
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File,
File Number 09A:
The Queen of Shiba.
Please look forward to it.
Therefore, he may have illegitimate children somewh...