Japan lost the war.
But humanity is strong.
I’m sure a city will be built over this burnt-down field and it’ll be bustling with people.
I plan to make Japanese Empire Security Service
a tractor for post-war reconstruction.
With it, I’ll create businesses operated by both government and private enterprise.
Eventually, this will lead
to a global corporation.
That’s my last job. I’ll dedicate
the rest of my life to it.
In other words,
you won’t support me.
Ruriko-san, you’re mistaken.
I’ll hate you.
I will hate you, Uncle.
You were right, Uncle.
The Japanese Empire Security Service is now a global company called JACES.
But I haven’t given up yet.
Please laugh at me for being a tenacious woman, Uncle Yakushiji.
Eleventh File
The Princess of Takanawa
Is my usual seat open?
It practically is.
We are in the training region.
Is it true that if your house is in a designated training region, no one can stay there anymore?
Yes.
It’s really troublesome.
So you’ve gone
for a walk, Monami.
Where to?
I’d like to speak
to you about Shiba.
Can we meet?
What? Right now?
I’ll go over there.
I’d like to report the results from my investigation so far.
But…
Oryou!
Why are you here?
I heard rumors that you
were sniffing around Shiba.
This has nothing
to do with you.
If you’re going to see Izumida,
I’ll give you a ride.
Why don’t you tell me the content of your so-called investigation report too?
I refuse.
It’s no use refusing.
I’ll find out once
I torture Izumida-kun.
The innocent Izumida-kun will end up suffering if you’re stubborn.
You’re really…
Say, do you intend to stay
quiet until we get there?
I can tell you if you answer
my question truthfully.
Is that so? In that case,
ask me anything.
First, regarding this woman.
Oh, Isurugi Ruriko.
What’s with your reaction?
Were you conducting your secret investigation without knowing her name?
Of course not!
Yes, I’ll be right there.
Izumida.
I wanted to see you.
C-Could you be…
Monami-chan?
Oui, monsieur.
Impossible!
Just the other day,
you were still…
Hey!
Have you already discovered the links between Isurugi Ruriko and NPP?
The Japanese Private Police, the second largest security company, splits the security industry market with JACES.
Ruriko is NPP’s
secret owner, you know.
Of course I know.
Right after the war,
my grandfather,
Yakushiji Masamoto, and Isurugi Ruriko tried to make Japan’s largest security service company.
But Ruriko was following
a secret agenda.
The plan was to hire ex-soldiers from army and navy units that disbanded at the end of the war
and remilitarize Japan under the cloud of a security service.
That’s absurd!
It’s not impossible.
In fact, all the private security service employees in Iraq right now are ex-soldiers.
That’s a different story.
Anyway, my grandfather refused to support Ruriko and built a company alone.
The Japanese Empire Security Service became the forerunner of JACES.
And what about
Isurugi Ruriko?
After she disappeared for
some time, she built NPP,
but her original plan
was never fulfilled.
And she hates the
Yakushijis for that.
In your case, there are many more who hate you besides her…
Wait a minute.
What’s wrong?
It’s strange…
Your face?
Isn’t it?
You said “right after the war”… how old does that make Ruriko?
I found this in the main house on Kamakura Mountain.
There are no traces of the photograph being altered at all.
I completely forgot about it.
Superintendent Muromachi
is headed here.
Monami-chan.
Izumida.
W-W-Wait!
What are you going to do
if someone sees us like this?
Th-That’s my line.
She’s here!
Assistant Inspector Izumida, it’s me.
Superintendent Muromachi,
right now I’m…
Is someone there?
No, that’s not the case.
Hey, wait!
What are you doing,
Assistant Inspector Izumida?!
This is a misunderstanding.
She’s…
She looks just like you!
Yes.
No, when I look carefully,
she’s a lot younger.
You don’t need to say
anything unnecessary.
Long time no see, Monami.
You’ve grown up a fair bit
while you were away.
Although it looks like
my breasts are bigger.
You don’t need to say
anything unnecessary.
I’ll help.
Thank you.
Who is she?
Oryou’s relative
or something?
I don’t know how
I should explain this…
Say, Monami, you should come to my place as originally planned.
No.
How come?
I know.
You’re trying to take me
somewhere far away.
So you knew.
I’ll stay with Izumida.
I’m going to live
here with Izumida!
Izumida-kun, what are
your thoughts on this?
Do you want to live
here with Monami?
Even if you ask me…
Then how about this.
Monami. Izumida-kun.
Both of you
come to my place.
But…
I’ll stop talking about taking you out of the country too.
Really?
What’s with that look?
You still don’t trust me?
In that case, do you
want to pinky-swear?
Izumida.
Does it taste good?
Y-Yes, it does.
I’m glad!
Izumida, you’re really lucky.
Since you can eat breakfast with a beautiful lady and a pretty girl.
It’s from Marianne.
When are those
two coming back?
They were both
in Paris, right?
Yeah.
I asked a perfumer I know
to make me a perfume,
but it looks like it’ll take
more time to complete it.
It’s a list of people who have entered and left the Shiba government building in the last two months.
I’ll take a look.
Did you notice something?
There are a few odd people.
They’re all people from the medical field,
a field that doesn’t have anything to do with Shiba.
They’re former executives
of the Tsukuyomi Party.
The Tsukuyomi Party?
They were controlling
human growth.
Ruriko probably used their research to make Monami grow up.
To begin with, what is
Isurugi Ruriko like?
I have to tell
that story again?
I just told the long story
to Oyuki the other day.
Unfortunately,
I didn’t hear it.
I know that!
Izumida-kun,
did you just laugh?
N-No, I did not.
Is that so? Then that’s fine.
This is a secret between
the two of us, okay?
Mistress Ryouko probably has feelings for Izumida-san.
To her, solving mysteries with Izumida-san is a time of love.
Just like how lovers talk about love,
they go about solving supernatural crimes.
What about Izumida?
What does he
think about her?
Izumida-san has yet to
notice her feelings for him.
But he should eventually.
And the two will be united.
Thank you very much.
I now have a general understanding of who Isurugi Ruriko is.
Now that leaves
three mysteries.
First is how Isurugi
keeps her youth.
The second is her relationship
with Monami-chan.
What is she planning to
do with Monami-chan?
The third is
Monami-chan herself.
Who exactly is she?
And the fourth mystery.
Superintendent!
Bear with it for a bit.
This is the only place
they’re not bugging.
Who exactly is the person
who set up the bugs?
Who do you think it is?
Umm, since we’re in this situation, please just tell me if you know.
Tsk.
You’re no fun.
Umm…
It’s Nonagase-kun.
Probably.
Can’t be!
Well, he’s the only outsider
who can enter here.
But why?
Either he’s just an enthusiast,
or he’s a spy that Ruriko sent in.
Either way, we need to
identify him and…
What are you doing?
J-Just… something…
So this is where you were.
You don’t seem too happy.
Is this regarding
Izumida-san?
You can consult
me if you like.
Really?
Of course you can.
Let’s go for a drive next
time we have a chance.
Look after the house?
Yes, that’s right.
We’ll probably
be late tonight.
Don’t wait up.
It’s me.
Where are we going?
There is someone
I want you to meet.
That’s the wagon.
Let’s follow it.
But why did she tell us to
follow her company’s car?
We won’t be dragged into
a strange case again, right?
Oh, keep a little
more distance.
Let an unrelated car come in between us from time to time.
Yes.
Maruoka-san,
you’re really into this!
It’s been a while since
I followed someone.
Should we let her know?
I’ll e-mail her.
Is she here?
Yes, she is.
See?
I was waiting for you.
Ah! She’s here!
They went inside there.
This is the only entrance,
so I doubt they’ve left.
Wait here.
What was that?
You saw it, didn’t you?
It’s strange.
It doesn’t feel like our
first meeting, even though it is.
It’s like I can
tell you anything.
The man you love…
… was it Izumida-san?
Yes.
I’m interested in what
he thinks of Ryouko-san.
It’s a defective product Ruriko-san made with great care,
but unfortunately it did not bear a soul, and its body rotted while it was alive.
We call it the living dead.
Gather the bones of the dead,
line them up in order
from head to toe.
Apply medicine by the name
of Hisou to the bones.
Hisou is Arsenic Trioxide.
After mixing with strawberry
and chickweed leaves,
tie up the bones with strings
from young Wisteria leaves,
and wash them
thoroughly with water.
Where hair should
exist on the head,
apply ashes of Gleditsia
and Hibiscus leaves.
Lay tatami mats on dirt,
and on them, lay the bones,
and organize them
before the wind breezes in.
After 27 days have passed,
go and burn
aloes and incense,
and conduct the
secret art of Hangon.
Hangon is the
revitalization of the dead.
The secret art of Hangon?
The secret formula to create man from corpses. It’s said that Saigyou Houshi had performed it.
As expected of Izumida-san.
You’re as knowledgeable about things like these as Mistress Ryouko.
Ruriko-san is a descendant of a noble who taught the secret arts of Hangon to Saigyou Houshi.
By mixing ancient, secret arts with modern
cloning techniques, we can create anyone we wish.
That’s impossible!
You don’t believe me?
You were with
her all this time.
With Ruriko-san’s creation.
It can’t be!
Me?
Yes, that’s right.
If you take the place of the current Ryouko-san and become Yakushiji Ryouko, everything will work out.
If I do, will Izumida love me?
I would think so.
Shooting without warning.
That’s just like you,
Ryouko-san.
Now that I’m unarmed,
whether it be grilling
me or torturing me,
do whatever you
want with me.
The people and events in this work are purely fictional.
Any resemblance to existing people or events is entirely coincidental.
I’d like to ask this
since we’re on the topic.
What is it?
Izumida-kun, you used to go out with a girlfriend whom you had the intention of marrying—
Yakushiji Ryouko’s Supernatural Case File,
File Number 09-D: Tokyo. Dead or Love (first part).
Please look forward to it.
Say, is she—