Cell fusion complete.
Turn left at the next intersection.
Superintendent, please take over the driving.
At least add a navigation system to the car.
Attentive people with normal memories don't need one.
I'm driving through unfamiliar streets.
That's why I'm navigating.
Thank you very much.
What are those photos?
We'll get on the highway after the next set of lights.
Which way to the highway?
Towards Musashino.
Which way is that?
Up.
Don't depend on others for everything.
If you look at the sun, you'll naturally know the direction.
It's common knowledge for a sailor.
I'm not a sailor.
The victim's a man.
He wasn't carrying any ID, so his identity is unknown.
Average build and height.
He was about 30 years old.
There's a severe laceration on his abdomen.
It looks like his organs were removed.
Oh, and he's holding a knife in his right hand.
[Note: The lullaby you'll be listening to throughout this episode is called Takeda no Komoriuta.]
Damn it, that Katsuragawa geezer!
What's wrong?  You couldn't see him?
They say he called in sick.
[Note: The Diet is Japan's legislative assembly.]
He fails as a member of the Diet.
Even members of the Diet sometimes get sick.
What?  You still haven't gotten over it?
It was a narrow street.  I'm sorry.
Didn't I warn you to be careful?  It's a narrow street.
I don't recall hearing such kind words.
You can't just change your memory on the fly.
That's what you  specialize in.
If you want to improve your memory, then you should start by not memorizing useless things.
Ready with the excuses as always.
Well, we'll just need to replace it.
How much will it cost?
Now, let's barge into Katsuragawa's house.
DK Pharmaceutical is known to be advanced, even within the industry.
Despite not being a large company, they have a long history and close ties with government institutions.
One rumor states that its founder was closely associated with the military during the war.
And then there's Katsuragawa Heizou, whose house is next door.
He's the chairman of DK Pharmaceutical
and has previously served as the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare.
He's a leading figure of the Minsei Political Party.
Yakushiji Ryoko tells me that she is going to meet Chairman Katsuragawa.
But as usual, I don't know anything about her objectives.
There are security guards.
He's a former minister, after all.
Do you think they'll let us in?
Hang on tight.
We're barging in.
Barging in?
I told you that we'd barge into his house.
No way!  Hey, Superintendent!
This is a nightmare!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
It's dangerous!
Right back at you.
Oyuki!
Superintendent Muromachi.
What's this about, Oryo?
A terrorist attack?
Or perhaps you're playing the role of a "cool" cop?
Move.
No, I will not.
Move!
I can't.
I'm here for work.
Work?
Are you guarding Katsuragawa Heizou?
Yes, I was assigned to.
Oh my, it must be hard to be working under someone.
You travel east and west, anywhere, whenever you're ordered to.
WTED Oryo?
Now of all times.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Well...
It's...
You've failed again?
I'm terribly sorry.
It's me.
Where are you right now?
This is absurd.
This is going to cost you.
Even from the outset, I didn't plan on it being free.
I don't understand you.
Katsuragawa Heizou.
What is this about?
Chairman, I'm terribly sorry.
I'm Yakushiji Ryoko.
I am aware of that.
Then that makes things easier.
Chairman, I've come here to ask you a few questions.
I'm a busy man.
54121.
I'm sure you know.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Besides, I'm not good with numbers.
Then, is it okay for me to speak here?
Although I don't know what lies you plan to tell,
I do know that they'll only embarrass you.
Let's have them decide whether I'm telling lies or not.
Behind me are all police.  They're not curious bystanders.
Come inside.
Oh, not you, Oyuki.
Why is that?
Just because.
I'll be accompanying him.
My job is to protect Chairman Katsuragawa from dangerous elements.
Who are you calling a dangerous element?
Yakushiji Ryoko.
Hey.
She's convincing.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Muromachi-kun, please wait outside.
Chairman!
Wait outside.
Geez, that Oryo.
What's that all about?
Yes, there are limits to being rash.
Oh, that's not what I meant.
I meant the number.
"54121."
Well, how much do you know about it?
Everything, of course.
And your objective?
I would like you to hand over 54121's data and all living artificial cells.
Artificial cells?
Bones?
From humans?
Eight years ago,
a joint expedition by the Japanese and French to investigate archaeological sites in Romania
found the skeletal remains of a primate.
At first, it looked human, but...
The next day, they used specialists and announced that it was fake.
Later, after they'd avoided the public's curiosity,
they distributed the bones for secret analysis amongst the G8.
And the one who took on the analysis in Japan was...
DK Pharmaceutical.
Its project code is 54121.
Your people extracted DNA from the unknown bones and artificially created animal cells?
And you concealed that fact.
I guess it's not a secret anymore.
What do you intend to do?
After we report the truth to the G8, JACES will take over the research.
JACES?
Please hand it over, Chairman.
Hmph, I see.
As expected from Yakushiji Ryoko.
I'm impressed.
Fine, I'll hand over all the research-related materials.
I lose.
Sorry I'm late.
According to Kishimoto,
no one told them anything special regarding Chairman Katsuragawa's protection.
Then, they were just guarding a VIP?
I'm surprised that convinced Oyuki.
Yes.
It seems that's why Superintendent Muromachi ordered Kishimoto to investigate the circumstances.
Treacherous girl.
Although they didn't find anything regarding DK Pharmaceutical,
they did find something about the Minsei Political Party.
It seems Katsuragawa Heizou has connections with the Yakuza.
Given his looks, I wouldn't be surprised.
And from there, we found out that four underlings of the Ginseikai were killed in the past three days.
And the culprit?
Currently still unknown.
Where were they found?
That's the thing.  They were all found in Inogashira Park.
I hear they were slashed across the abdomen and had their organs removed.
Izumida-kun.
Yes?
I think the latter part would have sufficed.
What?
Why do you give useless summaries?
Umm... I thought that the description shouldn't be simplified.
The way you explain...
I'm sorry.
I will keep that in mind.
If you're my subordinate, do it before I tell you to.
Yes.
So, what did you find out?
Yes!
DK Pharmaceutical had four research departments
and Yamagishi Yuuichi was responsible for all of them.
It looks like he manages 54121 too.
Here is Yamagishi-san's address.
Mitaka City, Shimorenja District...
What exactly is this?
Didn't we solve Chairman Katsuragawa's case,
since we're due to receive the data and the artificial cells?
That wasn't all of it.
"That wasn't all of it?"
You saw Katsuragawa's expression.
S-Stop!
Yeah, I will, if you jump from there!
Come on, jump!
Jump!  Now!
Why don't you?
Who are you?
So Katsuragawa asked you to silence him.
What are you talking about?
I was just...
I don't want to hear your improvised excuses.
Are you all right?
Who are you two?
Yamagishi-san, may I hear everything there is to know about 54121?
If you tell me, I'll guarantee your safety.
Hello?
What?  Really?
Katsuragawa has apparently disappeared.
We undertook a certain experiment after we created the cell.
An experiment?
The cell we created had the same number of chromosomes as humans.
So it was fused with a human cell.
If successful, it's possible that the mystery behind the organism may be revealed.
That's what we thought.
Did Katsuragawa order you to conduct the experiment?
I came up with it.
He was very happy with it, saying that it would change medical history.
Of course it would.
It's forbidden territory.
What did you specifically do in the experiment?
We fused the cell with a zygote created through artificial insemination.
Into a zygote?
You are Kimura-kun, right?
Yes, Katsuragawa-sensei.
The experiment was a success.
And an unknown organism was born.
As you can see, the organism's appearance was far from human.
Without a doubt, it isn't human.
Where is this organism right now?
Is it still alive?
Probably.
"Probably?"
Who provided the zygote for the cell fusion?
The ovum came from a woman in the research team.
Which one?
This one.
She's Kimura Keiko.
Who provided the sperm?
That's...
Was it you?
Yamagishi-san, did Kimura Keiko take the organism and run off?
Yes.
When?
Three months ago.
Where is she now?
I don't know.
I'm not involved in the search.
So Katsuragawa found Kimura Keiko and sent the Yakuza after her.
Why did he order them to kill her instead of capturing her?
If that organism's existence is publicized,
what do you think will happen to
Katsuragawa's status in society?
That's why he tried to conceal the evidence.
But he failed.
Did Kimura Keiko kill the Yakuza?
No.
Right?
Luckily, the police haven't found out about you two yet.
Please hand that organism over.
I'll guarantee your survival if you stay quiet about all of this.
Are you going to kill him?
It shouldn't have been born.
But he was.
But it's...
He's not an object.
He's my son.
Kimura-kun, are you insane?
You can't possibly think of him as your son.
He's my son.
"My son," eh?
Kimura-kun!
Where are we going?
Do you know where Kimura Keiko is?
Izumida-kun, you told me.
What do all the victims have in common?
The end of his reputation, huh?
Are you Kimura Keiko-san?
Yes, I am.
You are aware of why we are here, aren't you?
Yes, you're not here to kill me, right?
That's right.  We're here to end this.
End?
Yes.
This isn't the end.  It's the beginning.
This is just the beginning... finally.
You're finally free.  That's what you want to tell me, right?
Am I wrong?
W-We will arrest you and...
it .
"It?"
What do you mean by "it?"
He's not an object!
Izumida-kun!
No!  Don't!
He's my son!
Boy!
Here you go.
Coffee after an all-nighter?
You've got some nerve, trying to create pimples on my beautiful skin.
I thought you'd say that.
Geez.
Was that the right thing to do?
How is your injury?
It just scratched my arm a bit.
It doesn't hurt much anymore.
Then I think it was okay...
Probably.
Its cell tissues are fragile.
It won't live much longer.
Yakushiji Ryoko never spoke of this case hereafter.
Greetings, Oryo-sama.
Here comes the fan of leotards.
Is Hayama Eri-chan, the voice actress, making an appearance in this episode?
I'm talking about Eri-chan!  You know...
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File, File Number 05:
The Ox That Crawls the Omotesandou.
Please look forward to it.
Eri-chan is...