What a nightmare.
Lately, I've been having the same kind of nightmares.  I don't know why.
What unpleasant mornings.
My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.  33 years old.
A poor local government employee.
More specifically, I'm a lieutenant in the
Metropolitan Police Department.  I work under a counselor in the criminal investigation division.
All right.
Here you go.
Why, thank you.
Good morning.
Yes?
Izumida-kun, if you're in, come to my office right away.
I understand.
From the sound of it, she doesn't seem to be in a good mood.
I'm sorry it always has to be you.
Don't mind me.  It's my job.
Excuse me.
Izumida-kun.
I've told you before.
Come see me as soon as you clock in.
I'm terribly sorry.
This is my boss, Counselor Yakushiji Ryoko.
A career-minded bureaucrat who
graduated from Tokyo University.  She's an intelligent and skilled superintendent.
As for her appearance, it's what you see.
It's my job to babysit Yakushiji Ryoko, who aside from her personality, is perfectly flawless.
What business do you have with me?
This is not about business.
It is your duty as my subordinate to greet me, your master, first.
I will keep that in mind.
Izumida-kun.
Is there something else?
Where's your morning greeting?
Good morning.
Well done.
Then prepare to leave.
To where, may I ask?
Shopping in Ginza.
You're my shopping bag handler.
During work hours?
I can't use you unless it's during work hours, right?
We're caught in traffic.
I'm terribly sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not in a hurry anyway.
Hey!  Hang in there!
Oddly, whenever I'm with Yakushiji Ryoko, I'm confronted with supernatural cases.
There is one thing I still do not understand.
Were there any customers besides the victim?
No, no one.  He was my first customer today, after all.
It looked as though he was lost in
thought after he ate his breakfast.
He was creepy, so I didn't talk to him.
It's Lieutenant Konoma.  Remember?  He helped us at Pandemonium.
Oh, the Tokyo Nightmare case.
You named it?
We're going after him.
Wait!
What's all this racket about?
The police?
Secure the building at once.  A suspect has run inside.
That's absurd!
If you complain, you'll be arrested on a separate charge and thrown into jail!
That remark was unnecessary.
Owner!
If you're going to investigate my building, I would like you to follow the proper procedures.
You're telling me to bring a warrant?
That piece of paper's useless.
We don't have a warrant since this is an emergency.  Please cooperate with our investigation.
It's no use.  It seems the idiot doesn't intend to let us in at all.
Idiot?!
Owner Soga is...
A former elite bureaucrat in the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare, right?
Huh?
I've heard the rumors about you.
Your ability to blame your subordinate for everything
related to the drug scandal seven years ago forced him to commit suicide...
You did a fine job.
Yes, there were false rumors such as those going around.
[Note: Amakudari (literally: descent from heaven) describes the practice of bureaucrats retiring to lucrative positions in the private/public sector.]
So you've gone amakudari, playing king of the hill in this dirty building.
You bitch!  I've had enough!
Stop it!  Don't do it!
There.  You're under arrest for interfering with a government official in the execution of her duties.
I lose.
Fine, I'll cooperate with your investigation.
However, I would like you to refrain from securing the building.
In return, you'll be able to see every room in this building.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Then, if you'll excuse me.
[Note: Pomade is a substance used to make hair slick and shiny.]
That pomade geezer really pisses me off.
I'll definitely find his weakness and make him regret it to the depths of the ocean.
Lieutenant, I've found this.
As I thought, the QTR.
Quarantine Technical Research Organization.  QTRO for short.
Quarantine would mean it's under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare.
The pomade geezer we just met runs this place.
The QTR is just another place for amakudari.
I see.
What's more, I hear they sell the imported goods illegally and take the lion's share of the profits.
This country must be a civil worker's paradise.
More importantly, what should we do?
About what?
We should search for the suspect from earlier.
You can forget about him.
What?
I think we'll find something from the ring.
What a nice view.
Of course it is.  They ignored Ginza's rule while building it.
Ginza has a restriction on the height of buildings to protect its city vista.
But that Soga guy ignored the rule and built this Tower of Babel.
Old Testament all of a sudden?
They claim they couldn't hear the voices of opposition from the local people at all.
So that's why this is the Tower of Babel.
I'll wait over there.
Regarding the supernatural incident earlier...
Yes?
Can you tell me what you think?
People instantaneously aging and mummifying while alive...
At first glance, it's a mysterious supernatural case...
What do you think about this?
Even if you ask me...
Perhaps it's a little dull.
What if it isn't a supernatural case?
I believe it would be a criminal case where a suspect exists.
What about this?
Isn't that a little too showy?
And what makes you think that this is a criminal case?
Although it's not mentioned in any official document, the incident we encountered in Karuizawa...
The Visitor from Fog case?
You gave that a name as well?
What about this?
I believe that is made for teenagers.
Anyway, at the Karuizawa incident...
The Visitor from Fog.
What about...
...this?
You'll be showing too much skin.
You think?
During the Visitor from Fog case, we saw a drug that caused a very similar effect.
Perhaps the suspect used a similar drug?
I see.
So you like those kinds?
Ah... um, my button just...
I'll go try it on.
Let's assume your deductions are correct.
What is the suspect's motive?
That is still unknown.
He could have been after that man or it could have been an indiscriminate terrorist attack.
If it were the latter, there's a possibility that there will be a second attack.
Please don't say things like that.
However, my boss's ominous prediction unfortunately came true.
Izumida-kun.
I'll call you back again later.
This time, I hear there are six victims.
Is that so?
Perhaps the guy we let escape has made a second attack?
If that were the case, we would have caused a scandal.
Sorry to make you wait.
I've brought you the investigative report on the ring.
Thank you.
The ring that the suspect dropped belonged to a group known as the Tsukuyomi Party.
They're an occult group that believes in the existence of Tsukuyomi, the Goddess of the Moon.
Their representative is Kougetsu Reikou.
However, since he is still young, their organization is managed by a few executives.
I would like more details.
I agree.
I guess I'll make JACES investigate.
He must be an agent of the pomade geezer.
It seems so.
But still, he's overcautious.
He might have looked into your personality.
What do you mean by that?
We left Ginza and visited the inspector, Professor Tatsumi.
When it comes to
paranormal phenomena and supernatural cases, he's known to have an open mind.
He understood us very well.
You two again?
Professor, have you finished the autopsy?
I've just finished.
Since this case is supernatural, I did it at top speed.
And the cause of the death?
Before I tell you, you've brought it, haven't you?
Of course.
Ah, yes, this is it.
What is this?
It's the badge of the Tsukuyomi Party that we suspect is involved in the case.
Oh?  Is that so?
I thought I found something strange.
I've found food contaminated with poisons in his stomach.
How did the suspect add the poison?
He didn't add it.
The food was contaminated even before it was cooked.
What?
There were various kinds of contaminated food.
All of which were imported.
I see.
It seems the police have started to make their move behind the scenes.
This will be a big international problem,
so it doesn't look like something you guys should take on.
The culprit's probably the QTR.
What?
The QTR is the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare.  He went amakudari too.
That's right.
So you're saying that they're involved in this case?
I didn't say that.
What?
The quarantine of imported food falls under the jurisdiction of the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare, right?
That's why I'm going in under the pretext that this mummification case is their responsibility.
I'm going to run down that pomade geezer.
You're going to start a fight using evidence from this case?
It's not an ordinary fight.  I'm going to start a fight that I can win.
I thought you were working towards uncovering the truth.
I don't care about the case.
What?
Now I have a good reason to raid the QTR.
Then I'll just have to fight on the spot.
It's a den of amakudari, after all.
I'm sure it's filled with scandals.
Yakushiji-san, play with me like you did in the past.
Senpai!
That voice...
Oh, Oryo-sama is here too.  Hello.
Long time no see, Kishimoto.  Have you been well?
Of course!  I've started a new group with people I've met online.
The leotard...
Why are you here?
We're here for work.
"We"?
Which means she's also...
Superintendent Yakushiji!
My boss has an enemy.  It's Counselor Muromachi Yukiko.
She's also a superintendent, like Yakushiji.
Apparently, their ongoing rivalry began at Tokyo University, during their days as law students.
Oh my Oyuki, you've aged a fair bit since I last saw you.
And you.  Perhaps you've put on some weight?
Oh my, poor girl.
It seems like you're losing your vision due to age.
Are those reading glasses?
They are not!
You shouldn't get so mad.  It isn't good for your health.  You're not young, you know.
Enough of this, Oryo!
Shouldn't we stop them?
Then why don't you do it?
I'll be chairman for your funeral.
Please give me a break.
More importantly, what work did you come here for?
We're escorting a VIP.  There's going to be a party hosted by the QTR.
A party?
Oyuki, is that true?
I'm under no obligation to answer.
The fact that you're resisting means it's true.
Izumida-kun, we're going.
Y-Yes.
Call for reinforcements at once.
Why is that?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because trouble occurs wherever she goes.
Izumida-kun,
these are the invitations to the party.
How did you get ahold of them?
It's easy.
What are you going to do after we participate in the party?
You'll find that out later.
If all goes well, we might find the culprit.
What?
Can you zip it up, please?
Yes.
I understand.
Liquidate them.
As Tsukuyomi-sama wishes.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
"The deadline is extended!"?
What are you looking at?
No, nothing.
You were looking at me, weren't you?
I was wondering what was on your mind.
Oh, what a boring man.
Are you Mr. Izumida?
Yes?
I've received a message for you.
Excuse me.
It's from Superintendent Muromachi.
What is this?
She wants to meet Izumida-kun in secret?!
It's a little worrying.
Not at all.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me?
Because I am your subordinate.
Fine.  Go.
But you must tell me everything that the woman in charge of discipline says.
Got it?
Yes.
Izumida-san!
Kishimoto!
I'm sorry.  I was the one who called you.
They threatened me too.
Aren't you a member of the police?!
But...!
Do it!
Shall I make you something?
Please do.
Bastard!
Who ordered you?!
You look good in that tuxedo.
Cut the crap!
Seems like you'll look good in funeral clothing too.
Superintendent, don't!
What's wrong, hurrying up here?
You've finally revealed yourself.
I will have you tell me...
everything you know.
The people and events in this work are purely fictional.
Any resemblance to existing people or events is purely coincidental.
Superintendent, please give a preview comment in less than 15 seconds.
What?  That little?
It's impossible to explain my charm in such little time...
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File, File Number 02: Ginza Crime Tower (Part Two).
Hey Izumida, why are...