My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.
I am Yakushiji Ryoko's confidant...
or so it seems.
Today, I'm here with my boss at Narita Airport.
That's because...
Marianne, Lucienne.
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been a while.
It's great to see you again.
We missed you so much.
Marianne and Lucienne are two maids who work for Yakushiji Ryoko.
Of course, being maids, they do household chores, but that's not everything they do.
Marianne is an expert with weapons,
and Lucienne is an expert with computers.
She's a genius when it comes to hacking.
Say, Izumida-kun.
Why don't you stop dozing and join the conversation?
Unfortunately, I'm not good at speaking French.
This country sure doesn't change.
Corrupt politicians and bureaucratic scandals...
I'm surprised that this continues.
Of course it does.
People just complain instead of doing something about it.
People just stay in their territory and complain.
You're right about that, but...
But what?
I believe you do that too much , Superintendent.
What happened?
Superintendent!
That's...
If I knew this was going to happen, I would have brought my gun.
Oh my, perfect timing.
What are you saying?
How did it go?
I've notified the ones in charge at the Ginza Police Station.
Is that so?
More importantly, what if the room next to us is red and has futons ready?
How appropriate of you to play the role of the evil deputy official.
How rude.
I'm the sweet city girl who was kidnapped.
What do you think about the incident earlier?
I have no idea whatsoever.
One thing though.  The victim may have had connections with the mafia.
Why is that?
The gun he held was a Tokareva.
Close.
Even if it was a Tokareva, was it as crudely modified as the guns used by the mafia?
Let's let the Ginza police handle this for now.
That's great.
I'm sure your Cabinet minister will be very happy once we settle this.
Yes, he was pumped up about being able to use as much money as he wanted.
Two elite bureaucrats up to no good.
Do you know them?
Among bureaucrats, they're somewhat famous.
This one's Aoyama from the Ministry of Defense.  He's known as Mr. Dinner.
That one is Isogai from the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism.
He's like the runner-up.
So they have a cozy relationship with their dealers
who then take them out to dinner.
It's the opposite.
The saint's maids are quoting Latin.
After attending many dinners, they now
manage dinners for various other people.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where are those two?
They went home ahead of us.
They probably wanted to leave us alone.
Good night, Mistress.
We'll come again.
Good morning.
Izumida-san!
Izumida-kun!
What is it?
We've experienced it!
Oh Lord, protect us.
It was a ghost's doing!  I'm sure of it!
What's wrong?
Last night, we were sorting material in the reference room downstairs just like the superintendent instructed.
Oh my, is it an earthquake?
That wasn't an earthquake just now, was it?
Do you hear something?
So that's what happened?
It wasn't just the Metropolitan Police Department.
Jackie phoned me yesterday.
It seems a similar incident occurred at the Ministry of Finance.
Wakabayashi-san experienced it too?
I think it's just a cold.
I should be better tomorrow.
Yes, I'm terribly sorry.
No!
I'm scared!
They're waiting over there.
Thank you.
Let's go somewhere else.
We stand out too much here.
Just who are you calling a poikilothermic animal?
Just who?!
But Oyuki, you said you get cold hands and feet easily.
I wonder if your hands and feet are cold because you're cold inside.
If I'm a cold-blooded animal,
you're a merciless cold-blooded animal!
Oh my, there's no one as warm as me.
I'm surprised they don't run out of topics to argue about.
I'm sure it's like your hobby.  They won't get tired of it.
Oh yeah, regarding my hobby, the leotard...
More importantly, let's continue our conversation.
Yes, yes.
I may not look like it, but I'm a career bureaucrat, right?
Well sorry for being a non-career bureaucrat.
Now, now.
Among us career bureaucrats,
there have been rumors recently of ghost sightings and poltergeist phenomena.
It looks like similar incidents have occurred at each ministry and government office.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Oryo?
The Metropolitan Police,
the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism,
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
the Ministry of Finance,
the Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries,
and the Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry.
Thought so.
The subway.
The poltergeist causing the Kasumigaseki trouble is traveling via the subway.
Meaning the Hibiya Line?
No.
There's a line that connects Yurakucho Line's Sakuradamon Station with Chiyoda Line's Kasumigaseki Station.  Like this.
If this line is used to travel every night...
Yes, it does line up with the ministries and government offices where the ghost incidents occurred.
But you said "it."  Do you mean...?
That's right, the mysterious shadow we saw the other day.
Its identity is probably the...
...Underground Monster, Teradtron.
Again with "Mystery, Thursday the Twelfth?"
This way please, Master.
Oh, come in.
Leave that there.
Your men will regret it if they see their boss like this.
I don't understand this fetish either.
Good work.
You may leave.
Things will get out of hand if we don't finish it off quickly.
Even if we lied, blaming it on ghosts or poltergeists, there is  still a limit to it.
That's why you want to mobilize my soldiers again?
So that's how it is.
Via their head office, I've talked with Tokyo Metro.
You didn't have to get their permission.
Please tell me, Superintendent.
What's here under Kasumigaseki?
Just wait until you see it.
Izumida-san, please be careful.
I'm not worried since I'm with WTED Oryo.
But she's also SLD Oryo.
Yes, I remember now.
This way.
That's the line that connects Kasumigaseki and Sakuradamon.
We're just about underneath the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Superintendent!  Look at that!
Don't attack it!
Why?
Because it's Japan's natural treasure.
Is it the giant salamander?
Still, it's huge...
Is this...?
Yes.  This is the identity of Teradtron, the Underground Monster.
It doesn't look like it'll attack us.
Wait!
Normally, it eats small fishes and frogs, but it probably...
This way.
It must have made this hole the other day.
Where are we?
The Hibiya Common Utility Duct.
It's an underground facility to connect various utility lines together.
So this is it.
Who are you guys?
We're with the Metropolitan Police.
Police?
Get out of here.
You guys are the soldiers hired by the Ministry of Finance, the Ministry of Defense,
and the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism, right?
Bitch!  How the hell do you know about that?
Heh, I wonder.
It's the salamander!
This way.
Damn it.  It's here.
That's the one!
Call for reinforcements!
It probably thinks we're food.
No, it might have just followed you here for no reason, Superintendent.
Why's that?
Well, I just thought it did.
What the hell is this place?
The underground facility that was built by the Imperial Japanese Army in preparation for battles on the main island.
It was discovered during the construction of the Hibiya Common Utility Duct.
But the streets are...
They decided to build a giant resort facility that only bureaucrats could visit.
The public's eyes can't reach the underground.
Of course, it was built using the money embezzled by every ministry and government office.
That's tax money.
That's what it's called by the side who pays.
The side that uses it doesn't think so.
Superintendent!
There's no doubt about it.  It's after you.
Why though?
Superintendent!
Come with us, Officer.
If I remember correctly, you're Izumida-kun.
How do you know my name?
You're WTED Oryo's subordinate, aren't you?
Actually, I have something to ask you...
no, the two of you.
Over here!
Our plan has suffered a setback due to the appearance of that monster.
The two of you are well known, even within the Ministry of Defense.
I hear the two of you are fairly strong.
If you have confidence in your strength,
I would like to ask you to exterminate that monster.
What did you say?
Of course, I will guarantee a return worthy of its price.
I don't want to say this, but you're a non-career bureaucrat.
The difference between you and the career bureaucrats will only grow bigger as you age.
How about it?
If you're going to live as a non-career bureaucrat, why not lend us a hand?
You won't be sorry.
I will also promise you success in life.
I don't think it's a bad deal for you.
I decline.
But, listen...
I am satisfied with being Yakushiji Ryoko's subordinate.
Bastard!
Taking the upper hand just because we were being modest!
You bitch!
Bye bye!
That's...
What is this?
Damn you!  How dare you!
Above!
Superintendent!
Wait.
I've asked Abe Jun-san for reinforcements.
He said he'll be here soon.
They should just be locked up for life underground with the natural treasure.
Okay.  Start it.
Roger.
An underground water vein?
Lucienne found it using data from the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism.
Maybe it knew you'd do this.
Impossible.
Assistant Inspector Izumida, what are you reading?
Ibuse Masuji?
[Note: "Sanshouuo" is Japanese for "salamander."]
"Sanshouuo."
What is it about?
I believe it was about a salamander which became too big to get out of its den.
It complained and gave excuses.
I read it when I was a student too.
Yes, that was what it was about.
People just stay in their territory and complain.
I heard from the girls.
You declined their offer, I hear?
Yes.
You said you were satisfied with your current position, right?
Th-That's...
You did say it, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Why did you say something so stupid?
What?
If you had brought the natural treasure under your control
and had beaten Mr. Dinner up, I could have been ruling his underground world.
Man, what a waste.
Saying those things again...
Besides, their money is...
No excuses.
As punishment, treat me to dinner at the restaurant we went to the other day.
Of course, treat them too.
Man, I'm starved.
Yes, so are we!
Since Izumida-kun's paying for this tonight, let's order the chef's special.
Excuse me.
Inspector Maruoka!
How about we go for a drink?  Let's keep it a secret from the Superintendent, okay?
It's great to drink while complaining about your boss...
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File,
File Number 07:
Okinawa, God's Island.
Please look forward to it.
And?  What were you going to do?
Wh-What...