My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.
I am Yakushiji Ryoko's slave.
The supernatural incident that took place in broad daylight
was a result of imported, contaminated cooking ingredients.
While following the case, we were attacked by mysterious assassins.
Who were those people?
How did you know that she was trying to kill you?
What is your name?
Mizoroki Kikuno.
Who hired you?
Then let me rephrase my question.
You're involved in the mummification incident, aren't you?
Why did you do something like that?
An experiment.
An experiment?
An experiment for a divine goal!
What?
They attacked you too?
Yes.
It was a man named Terashima, the one who was with the owner, Soga.
And?  Did you beat him up?
I had Kishimoto detain him.
Izumida-san!
Hey, what about those guys?
Actually, they hit me on the head after you left.
Soga-san saved me while I was unconscious.
I am terribly sorry for what Terashima, my former subordinate, did.
"Former?"
I can't keep someone like him at my side.
After thinking about it, I fired him at noon today.
But it seems he blamed you for everything.
Basically, you're saying that you had nothing to do with the attack on Izumida-kun.
I'm only telling the truth.
If necessary, we may discuss this with my lawyer.
There is no need.
I'll reveal your true identity eventually.
Getting more information from her would have been nice.
Still, we were able to get a valuable statement.
It's just one phrase.
Do you remember what she said?
I recall her saying something about an experiment.
That's right.
If this series of incidents is an experiment, they'll need to gather data.
There is only one place they can do that.
I have been waiting for you, Mistress.
Izumida-kun.
Yes?
This is Nonagase-kun from JACES.
Good afternoon, Izumida-san.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Isn't it great?
I made it using my computer.
Nonagase-kun is a security maniac.
What's that?
You know how there are enthusiasts for police-related things, right?
Yes.
Please think of me as a security enthusiast.
I see.
And that hobby caused him to join my company.
He's hardcore, isn't he?
Ah, I see.
JACES is Asia's biggest security company.
Not only does it manage security, but it has also
appeared in other fields alongside its slogan, "Safety."
It has developed into a major corporation with annual revenues of 500 billion yen.
Yakushiji Ryoko is the daughter of Yakushiji Hiroki, Owner and President of JACES.
In line to be its next president,
she obviously owns stock in JACES.
She receives a yearly dividend of 300 million from them.
I'm way beyond envious.
That's strange.
What's wrong?
Professor Tatsumi's phone has been busy the entire time.
Professor Tatsumi.
Mistress.
It's from JACES.
Now things make sense.
That pomade geezer is an executive of the Tsukuyomi Party.
He was introducing chemicals into the materials sold illegally by the QTR.
Even if the incident was uncovered, he knew the exporting countries would be suspected.
But why would he do something like that?
All crazy groups do the same thing.
More importantly, what are they experimenting for?
It's not the time to be asking questions anymore,
since we've found our opponent.
What are we going to do?
Isn't it obvious?
We fight.
The security is tight.
Obviously.  The VIPs that attended the party are staying here.
Let's go.
Before we do, may I have a word?
What is it?
Please take better care of yourself.
You would be dead if Mizoroki Kikuno had poisoned your drink.
So what?
I believe she still could have done it.
Please refrain from this kind of reckless behavior.
Would it inconvenience you if I died?
Would it inconvenience you if I disappeared?
Of course.
You're my boss, after all.
There's no way I'll die.
But...
No matter what, I can't possibly die yet.
And?
Huh?
You know what to say at times like this.
You should say, "I won't let you die."
That's how a loyal servant should think.
I-I see.
Go!
Oh, it's just you, Mari-chan.
Ow!
Come on, spit it out.
Or else...
Why are you here, Mari-chan?
Supporting the security department.
What about you two?
The usual.
I see.
So this is the list of ingredients the QTR imported for cooking?
Yes.
Are there more?
No, Ma'am.
Really?
Yes.
Take this to investigation headquarters.
I'm sure they'll act right away if you tell them that it's evidence for the Mummy case.
Yes, Ma'am!
And take him too.
An underling like him will only get in the way.
Now, let's head back too.
Why?
"Why?"
Now that we've prevented more incidents from occurring,
we don't have any reason to stay here.
Huh?  What are you talking about?
This is where it all starts.
"Where it all starts?"
Bingo.
Looks like it's the drug.
What should we do?
Since it's a nice opportunity, I'll take them all.
I don't understand how this is a nice opportunity.
I feel like I'm stealing while there's a fire.
No, we aren't.  This isn't a fire.
You won't deny the thievery part though, right?
Wait.
I see...  A fire, eh?
Oh Tsukuyomi-sama, Dweller of the moon, please bestow the moon's blessing upon us.
Oh man, it hurts.
I'm going to interrupt your "fun."
Do you remember me telling you that I would reveal your true identity?
What was that noise just now?
I-I don't know.
Welcome, Yakushiji Ryoko,
to our experimental room!
Oh, an experimental room?
It seems you've got a lot of spare time on your hands,
demolishing a room in a high-rise building and
making something like this.
Oh?  You guys have monsters too?
Human mummification chemicals are basically growth enhancers.
If applied to reptiles, it'll unleash their endless growth.
They are the perfect animals for our experiment.
What is this experiment for?!
Our goal is to create an Ochimizu!
An Ochimizu?
[Note: A Man'yoshu is a collection of poetry.]
He's referring to the holy water that appears in the Man'yoshu.
It's in the hands of Tsukuyomi, the Goddess of the Moon.  Apparently, it can grant eternal life.
That is correct.
If the Ochimizu is completed, we'll be freed from the pain of growing old and dying.
An eternal paradise will thrive on this land.
But it's just a paradise for you guys, right?
Of course.
Only those who are like-minded...
That's enough.
I already know that you're a crazy scatterbrain.
You guys have two options.
[Note: The thirteen stairs here refers to the thirteen stairs to the gallows.]
Either you admit your crimes and climb the thirteen stairs or you face my punishment, right here, right now.
I recommend the latter,
since you can go to hell watching my beautiful face.
Then I choose the third option.
Bring him here!
That's...!
Professor Tatsumi!
Izumida-kun!
You're alive, Professor?!
What exactly is going on?
Well then, may I ask you to lower your gun?
I knew that it would turn out like this.
Izumida-kun, we'll use our trump card too.
Th-That's...!
This is the medicine you created after a lot of hard work.
How about exchanging the professor for this?
Idiots.
I can make more.
Right.  That's if  you can.
What?!
How about it?
Feel like negotiating?
Free him.
Yes, Sir!
Y-You saved me, Izumida-kun.
Professor, please hurry!
Superintendent!
Tatsumi-sama!
I knew it.  You were the real culprit, Professor.
How?
How could you tell?
Back then.
You mistook the badge I brought with yours, didn't you?
And Soga attacked us soon after we met you.
Until then, she was just watching us.
Why did she suddenly attack?
It's simple.
After you heard that I would meddle with the QTR, you ordered Soga
to finish us off.
That's when I was sure.
So you tricked me.
Yes.  I thought it was possible after the badge incident.
Too bad.
We've known each other for so long too.
To create eternal life.
For all of my life, that was what I sought.
The Tsukuyomi Party supported me.
Thanks to their support, my long-sought dream was about to become a reality.
I won't let the likes of you
interfere!
Now!
Shoot!
Are they dumb?
Do they intend to kill Professor Tatsumi too?
Don't ask me.
Wh-What's this?
What's happening?
Hey, stop this!
Tatsumi-sama!
Damn it!
Remember this, Yakushiji Ryoko.
One day...
One day, you'll also...
Fear not the strands of white.  Seek out the Ochimizu.
He said earlier...
that reptiles grow endlessly.
[Note: An ampoule is a small, sealed jar used to hold a solution for hypodermic injection.]
Then, if all those ampoules inside the snake break...
Izumida-kun, run for it!
I've received confirmation.
Everyone has evacuated safely.
Thank goodness.
We can't go down.
This way.
"This way?"
Where are we going, Superintendent?
You called a taxi?
What are you talking about?
We're on the roof.
A taxi won't...
I see.  A flying taxi.
It seems we've arrived at the entrance too soon.
I won't let heretics like you
interfere.
I won't let you interfere!
H-Hey!
Tsukuyomi-sama!  Please save me!
I see it.
Oh no, the helipad is...
Well then, I'm counting on you to escort me.
That's a servant's job.
I see.
Izumida-kun!
Oh shit!
Superintendent!
Izumida-kun, catch me.
No way...
You're jumping?
Yes, I am.
That's absurd!
It's too dangerous!
No, that's not it.
I told you what to say in these situations.
I won't let you die!
Well done!
See?  I told you so.
I can't die yet.
Thank goodness you're safe.
I'm surprised it didn't collapse.
It's a total disaster on the inside though.
But it'll be bulldozed after being damaged like this, right?
You sound like it's none of your business.
It is none of our business.
I think the local people will be happy too.
Superintendent Yakushiji!
Explain to me what happened!
The Tower of Babel was punished.
The snake was sent by Heaven to punish the
people seduced by Eve in the Garden of Eden.
Of all people, I'll let you give the official announcement.
Make sure that it is reasonable and logical.
Again?
Again, it was a crime only WTED Oryo could solve.
WTED Oryo?
That's what she's called in the
Metropolitan Police Department.
It stands for Oryo Walks Through Even Dracula.
Ah, that's why it's WTED Oryo.
Yes, it's a perfect nickname for Mistress Ryoko.
What was that preview last week?
You've appeared, Ms. Discipline.
To begin with, a preview is supposed to briefly and
accurately explain the next episode's story to the viewers.
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File, File Number 03:
[Note: Sakurada Gate is a nickname for the Metropolitan Police Department.]
Sakurada Gate Case.
Lieutenant Izumida...