Monami is my trump card.
She will eventually become the next president of JACES, as Yakushiji Ryouko.
Ruriko-san?
In that case, what'll happen to me?
I will make you disappear, of course.
Superintendent!
Izumida!
Izumida-kun, behind you!
That's your friend.
What do you mean?
Monami, don't listen to what she says!
The first time, I made you in France.
However, she was mentally dysfunctional and...
The second time, we failed to splice the DNA, and you can see the result in its expression.
And the one who finally succeeded is...
You are a living doll that I've created.
You are not human.
No... can't be...
That's a lie!
No!
Monami-chan!
Ruriko, you're despicable!
Izumida-kun!
Superintendent!
Monami, you wanted to know Izumida-san's true feelings, didn't you?
Izumida-kun!
He used himself as a shield to protect Ryouko-san.
You know what this means, right?
Even if the two of you share the same face and the same genes,
in the end, you're just a living doll.
I wonder whom Izumida-san will choose... you or Ryouko-san?
You will kill Ryouko-san and become Yakushiji Ryouko.
That is your only option.
Superintendent, are you hurt?
Don't talk!
I see you're fine.
I'm glad.
Now go on.
Superintendent!
Are you two all right?
Oh no, Izumida-san's injured!
Oh my goodness.
Let's go.
Oh no, it's really stuck in him!
Abe-kun, carry him for now.
Yes.
Izumida-san, this is bad!
She can be useful.
As my consciousness faded away, I'm sure I saw Yakushiji Ryouko smile.
Why did she make that expression?
How is he?
The doctor has prescribed bed rest for him.
You surprised me that night.
You suddenly appeared and told me to call a doctor.
I just had the emergency treatments done at the hospital and then headed straight here.
We're up against that woman.
We can't hospitalize him in some random hospital.
But still, preparing a second Ryouko-chan and switching her with the real one to take over JACES...
Ruriko-san sure did come up with something dreadful.
If I had two young tomboys like you as sisters, Ryouko-chan, I'm sure I would have had a hard time.
That's not the problem.
All the facilities related to JACES in the prefecture are within anti-terrorist practice areas.
We plan to deploy an elite unit of 150 men from NPP on the day of the practice.
It should be easy to suppress JACES's facilities if NPP and SDF work together.
I'll eventually dispose of these four who are related to Yakushiji Ryouko too.
Once Ryouko-san dies, we'll apply growth treatment to Monami and get her to take over JACES's management.
And as originally planned, I will have you enter the Yakushiji family as Monami's husband.
I understand.
Mistress Monami, like Yakushiji Ryouko, had the ability to summon things not from this world.
That's God's power.
By marrying Mistress Monami, I can get my hands on the power I...
I long for!
Izumida.
Well, I'm going now, Izumida-kun.
I'm about to go to war and risk my life,
so why are you asleep now?
You fail as a subordinate.
You must be punished.
On second thought, I'll punish you after I defeat Ruriko.
Wait here quietly.
Well, it's normal that you'd be surprised.
You were called and told up front that people are after your life.
Shiba will start its operations by going after your life.
The Shiba government building?
Why is that?
Because you three saw the Queen of Shiba, Isurugi Ruriko, in person.
Things have turned out just as I feared they would.
Oryo-sama, I don't have a clue as to what's going on.
Well, you've got nothing to do with this.
Actually, I don't remember calling you.
Why are you here?
But now that you've heard my story, I can't guarantee your safety.
Keep that in mind.
What?!
N-No way...
Don't make shameful sounds like that.
I'm a complete bystander, yet I'm prepared to lend a helping hand to Oryo-chan.
That has nothing to do with me!
Oryo-sama, what exactly is going to happen to me...
I'm not convinced either.
Yes, I was investigating Shiba,
but it doesn't seem like they've noticed at all.
Why is that?
Oyuki, do you remember Nonagase-kun?
Nonagase-kun?
Oh, the man who drove us to Nerima the other day?
He was actually a spy.
What?!
I suspected he was, but you talked about Ruriko in front of him without knowing, remember?
That was a fatal mistake.
No way...
If he was suspicious, why didn't you tell me beforehand?
Isn't that obvious?
I kept quiet on purpose to drag you into this.
Come with me for a minute.
I've decided to crush Shiba.
Shiba?
Since we are alike, this will be a big job which will put my life at risk.
Although we already know that I'll win.
Are you going to fight alone?
Against Shiba.
I'm not alone.
There's another one.
An old lady who's always a nosy, stubborn Ms. Discipline.
Take care of everyone for me, Oyuki.
Oryo.
You're Yakushiji Ryouko-san, right?
Ryouko-san, you're famous now, so you can't move around freely like you once did.
Damn that Ruriko.
I'll be back.
Reporting from the Main Observatory.
We've completed the connection.
All right.
Then evacuate everyone in the tower and secure the front entrance.
Roger that.
We're not going to leave anyone at the scene?
If someone's nearby, it apparently causes the system to malfunction.
I've brought her.
Monami, brand Ryouko-san's end into your memory.
There she is!
It's Yakushiji Ryouko!
Stop!
I heard gunfire over there!
Which way?
Who's calling at a time like this?
Just when I was wondering which idiot it was, it was that one.
Oryo-sama won't answer!
What are you crying about?
You're a cop, aren't you?
Get a hold of yourself!
So is everyone else!
We should have left Tokyo right away!
Even if you say that, everyone was busy with preparations.
Everyone, over here.
Hurry!
As expected from Ryouko-san.
She's fighting well by herself.
Request backup.
She fell into the river!
We've lost track of Yakushiji Ryouko!
She'll show herself again soon.
I wonder what...
...happened to Oyuki and the others...
These are...!
Izumida-kun!
Hello?
It's me.
We've received reports from the Shirogane Takanawa Observatory.
One civilian vehicle has entered the area.
Requesting orders.
Izumida.
Follow that car.
I'm glad you're fine, Superintendent.
Who do you think I am?
Superintendent!
Just a little bit...
Let me rest just a little bit.
Sure.
Yakushiji Ryouko's smiling.
Did that woman sign a contract with the Devil or something?
We've hurt her so much.
How can she still be smiling?
I know...
...why she is strong.
The reason is...
What is it?
I just thought that you're really strong.
Did you just notice?
Even though you've fought alone the whole day, you still look like this.
You're really amazing.
Notice me one of these days.
Did you just say something?
It's strange.
When I'm with you, I get the feeling that a crisis of this level is nothing.
That's my...
It's nothing.
You're right.
I'll stop a tank with the wink of an eye.
I hear that they're going to construct a new
Tokyo Tower in the Sumida District.
It's the Tokyo Sky Tree that's planned for completion in 2011.
I guess it's okay.
Yakushiji Ryouko's Supernatural Case File,
Final File:
Tokyo. Dead or Love. Part 2.
Please look forward to it.
What? I...