I am the Russian Empire's only legitimate monarch.
Follow me if you want to protect the Empire's future!
Hey! Izumida!
Why are you so dense?
My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.
I am Yakushiji Ryouko's loyal retainer...
Or so it seems.
This job usually keeps me very busy,
but even I have days off.
Was today...?
Let's hope nothing happens today.
Izumida-kun usually handles this task.
We should at least try our best to...
Superintendent Yakushiji!
What is with this tight schedule?
Well, we tried to...
...set it up as best we could.
How is it?
Rejected.
I think I'll go drink some awful coffee at Pastel.
It's already so late...
It's still so early...
Oh my, Oyuki. It's been a while.
Superintendent Yakushiji!
Oryou-sama!
Have you two come for tea?
I envy incompetent people like you
who have so much free time.
Neither do I have free time nor am I incompetent.
We have a press conference at eleven o'clock to discuss the case from the other day.
We were busy in the morning, so...
Why is the security division organizing the press conference?
I'm surprised you asked.
You're the one who forced me to clean up this case.
Then do you want me to attend the press conference too?
I'm sure it'll cause an uproar if I tell the press what actually happened.
Um, was it at eleven?
There is no need for you to attend.
Would it inconvenience you?
I just don't want more headaches.
Is that so?
In that case...
I am at the Metropolitan Police Department, where a press conference on the collapse of the Ginza building is being held.
There is much speculation regarding this incident, but the official explanation...
...is that a gas leak caused
an explosion in the building.
If there are no more questions, I will be ending this conference.
Is that all right?
No objections.
Oh, may I ask one thing?
There were reports of a JACES helicopter being present at the scene.
Is this true?
Please answer me.
Wasn't that a bad idea, Senpai?
What was?
It seemed that asking about it was taboo.
As journalists, uncovering the truth must be our only concern.
We can't write good articles if we worry about what others think.
May I have a word with the two of you?
That reads "Mitsutoshi".
So you two are reporters from Maichou Daily?
Yes.
Let me get straight to the point.
Do you know about WTED Oryou?
As you mentioned earlier, Yakushiji Ryouko will inherit JACES one day.
H-Hey.
JACES is where most people end up working after they retire from the Metropolitan Police Department.
Basically, if they oppose her,
they lose their jobs after they retire.
The elevator's full.
Wait for the next one.
No, it's okay.
This is where I get off.
That's not all.
I hear she uses JACES to uncover secrets and spread rumors about her superiors.
Therefore, everyone's scared of Yakushiji Ryouko.
You mean the Superintendent General too?
There is no hope for that man.
If one eats persimmons, red dragonflies will soar in the autumn sky.
Other than using sarcasm, even I can't do anything more to oppose her.
Why is that?
It seems she's got dirt on my company's superiors too.
I see. So even Nitto Daily...
Maichou Daily should be more or less the same.
Anyway, you shouldn't lay your hands on her.
If you provoke her, she may take it out on us too.
Well, I'm counting on you.
I get the feeling that his Kansai dialect is all fake.
Senpai, you've been quiet the whole time.
What's on your mind?
It's inexcusable.
As a journalist...
No, as a human, I'm angered by Yakushiji Ryouko's existence.
We ought to write an article about her and appeal to the public's sentiments.
But if Uesugi-san told us the truth,
any article we write would just be suppressed.
That's true.
How about this?
And? What did they say?
That they would stalk you and try to capture the moment.
Is that so?
Their plan is to reveal your scandal, gain public sentiment and then apply pressure on you.
To play "paparazzi"...
The renowned Maichou Daily sure has fallen low.
But I guess the press is the same everywhere.
It's like a cauldron of irresponsibility and fiction,
topped with jealousy and curiosity.
Ah, I know!
If he's dense, I could always do the grunt work and prepare.
I see.
It just might work out.
Maybe I've caught a cold.
I feel cold all of a sudden.
How is it?
It's very well written.
I'm impressed.
Really?
It's really motivating to hear that from you, Izumida-san.
Are you planning to write a report for every case Yakushiji Ryouko has been involved in?
Yes, since the official police records will cover up what really happened.
Mistress Ryouko is cooperating with me too.
Also, I've come up with a new nickname for her.
What is it?
[Note: SLD is short for "Summons Like Dracula".]
SLD Oryou.
SLD?
That's right.
I get the feeling that she has the power to summon unearthly things, much like Dracula.
SLD Oryou, eh?
Next station is Sakuradamon.
Please watch your step.
The doors on the right will open.
One more minute.
Hello—
Where are you?
Come to the street in front of the police department at once.
How was your break?
It was relaxing.
I see.
Then I will act out the ending to your enjoyable day off.
I'm prepared.
What do you mean by that?
Umm...
It wouldn't make a good picture if a man and woman walked separately after five o'clock.
Hmm, a shot from the back.
It wouldn't make a good picture.
We've got plenty of opportunities.
Let's go.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is with that outfit?
You don't know?
If you don't know, let me tell you.
This is called a China dress.
That's not what I meant.
Izumida-kun, can't you do better than ask stupid questions?
You look wonderful in that.
Rejected.
You're missing the "very".
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
I'll come again.
What do you want to do now?
I'm going to return home.
Like I said...
What do you want to do now?
Let's go get a drink.
Is that so?
If you say so, then I guess I have no choice. Let's go.
Say, Izumida-kun...
Yes?
I'm cold.
It is almost autumn.
Please wait a moment.
Oh...
Are you just opening up?
Ah, you two...
It has been a while.
You were late opening up today, weren't you?
It's really embarrassing, but the scandal from the other day is still affecting me.
The incident regarding the Ministry of Finance, Bureau of Accounts?
Yes.
There are a lot of those lately.
Misconduct by government bureaucrats.
It's really deplorable.
Although it's convenient for me.
How about this angle?
Therefore, it's all thanks to Ryouko-chan that I was able to find my true self, Jacqueline.
You've told me that story many times already.
Oh my, I'm embarrassed.
Then tell me so.
Jun-chan, you meanie.
I think I'm a little drunk myself.
I think I'll go home.
Is that so?
Jackie-san, can you lend me money for the taxi ride?
Hey, Izumida. Saying things like that again...
You're going to stay at my place.
No, that's...
Oh my, the two of you are going to be man and woman tonight.
Please don't say such depressing things.
I have cute maids too.
Oh, right.
Your paycheck hasn't arrived yet.
Why don't you stay at her place?
We are too late.
Up there.
Want something to drink?
No, thank you.
Are those two already asleep?
Oh, they're in Paris.
What? But earlier you said they were around.
I didn't say they were at home.
Perfect.
They're watching a video together.
It's probably some romance movie.
So this is the show you so often talk about.
Yeah.
"Mystery. Thursday the Twelfth."
They put a lot of money into this episode, so it's perfect for the uninitiated.
But it's really stupid, so be prepared.
I see.
Episode 14: Monster Teradtron Appears.
Listen, Imp God.
The spies I've sent to Earth have brought back information
that the foolish earthlings are inventing a weapon of mass destruction.
See? It's really stupid, isn't it?
Since it has come to this, we imps should stand up and...
No, it's interesting... in its own way.
Nothing's happening.
They've come out.
What?
Izumida-kun.
Sit there.
Perfect position.
It's too good to be true.
Maybe she actually knows about us?
Impossible.
Aren't you going to sit down?
Umm...
So you're that kind of man.
A man who makes me sit on a bench that's wet with evening dew.
You don't respect your boss at all, do you?
Got it!
Say, Izumida-kun...
You're fairly drunk.
Can't I be?
What are you doing?
I believe you should sleep.
Take me there then.
I don't want to walk.
Carry me to my bed.
Fine.
Wait.
Wh-What?!
Oh, I forgot something!
Superintendent!
We've arrived at the scene.
Secured two suspicious individuals.
We will now—
It's me.
Leave the two alone.
Just leave!
Right. Roger that.
What was that just now?
B-Beats me...
What's with that outfit?
The first train leaves around this time.
Oh well.
Although they didn't capture a perfect moment, I'm sure they got decent photos.
Umm...
What is it?
I will ask you one thing, even though I know that you won't answer me seriously.
What was that commotion just now?
No comment.
Thought so.
I understand.
Now, if you would excuse me...
What is it?
You have more questions?
What a persistent man.
Thank you for tonight.
Good night.
He's dense, but he knows what to say in situations like this.
It's really unsettling.
Wh-What the hell is this?
This is impossible!
A-All the d-data is gone.
Th-That can't be.
I'm scared!
And that's how my day off ended.
I would like to take it easy on my next day off, but, with her as my boss, that's probably impossible.
The people and events in this work are purely fictional.
Any resemblance to existing people or events is entirely coincidental.
Have some tea, Superintendent.
What's this?
It's Yuanyang, tea from the country I love, Hong Kong.
You mix coffee and tea—
Yakushiji Ryouko's Supernatural Case File, File Number 04: Musashino Violet Time.
You can also add—