[Note: The song being sung in the background is an Okinawan folk song.]
Why is Sanpin Tea the only tea all those vending machines are carrying?
Izumida-kun!
Geez, where did he wander off to?
My name is Izumida Jun'ichirou.
During the fifteen minute boat trip,
I was fortunate enough to have some time to myself in the car.
That's more than I can say for the man in bandages.
He didn't know that Yakushiji Ryoko's scarf included
a thread as tough as a diamond, a thread made from carbon fiber.
It would have been a perfect crime
if I had just "tripped" on the fire
extinguisher and "fallen" off the ferry.
Too bad.
You still did this even after knowing that I'm Counselor
Yakushiji Ryoko of the Metropolitan Police
Department's Criminal Investigation Division?
Transformation Technique?
Move!
Superintendent!
Assault.
The attempted murderer was caught red-handed.
Attempted murder?  You did?
Does it look like I'm trying to kill the witness?
Why did you park all the way back here?!
You told me to go in first.
We're going out first too!
I'm first!
S-Superintendent!
By the way, Superintendent, are you really here on vacation?
You sure are persistent.
It's not that.  Wouldn't I just be a nuisance if that was the case?
My.
Isn't ensuring your boss's safety during a vacation a part of the job description too?
So this is the mangrove.
It sure does come in various shapes.
Mangrove is a general term used to describe the plants and vegetation that grow in brackish water.
This water, for example, exists in the mouths of rivers
where the fresh water from swamps mixes with salt water.
Even a palm tree would be considered a mangrove if it grew here.
I see.
What was that just now?
Mangrove seeds germinate while still on the tree.
When they fall, they get embedded in the mud.
It's called a vivipary seed.
That's probably what made the sound.
I see...
Tadomura Family, stop destroying nature!
Yeah, stop it!
Stop the destruction!
The mangrove is an important place where we make offers to God!
Don't destroy it with your selfish construction!
Oh my.  With this, the tourist spot is ruined.
Stop screaming on private property.
You bought the local government and used force to build this!
That's right.  That's right.
We are abiding by the law.
We aren't destroying nature.
People from the mainland are building hotels and villas that don't fit the area.
That in itself is destroying the island!
The mangrove doesn't only belong to the Tadomura Family!
Bring us to Mr. Tadomura!
Bring us to him!
What are you doing?
That was just too rough!
He's right!  It was rough!
A tourist?
You're... um...
We met at Aoyama Broadway.
What?
You're still alive?
Hey.
He's the one who attacked me on the ferry.
No way!
[Note: The N in NPP stands for Nippon, another word for Japan.]
This villa belongs to Tadomura Ryoujun, the founder of NPP, the Japanese Private Police.
It's not surprising to see NPP security guards.
Superintendent, did you intend to investigate this place all along?
Superintendent!
It seems NPP is planning something.
Sis, the government has sponsored the creation of a company called NPP to take away JACES's market share.
They envy our success.
Tadomura is a former Diet member.
They've meddled with us before.
Have you heard?
Tadomura Ryoujun locked himself up in his villa in Okinawa
and hasn't come out of hiding for six months now.
I also hear he's causing trouble for the environmentalists on the island.
If we find out why Tadomura locked himself up,
we might get our hands on NPP's weakness.
Oh my.  You're scary.
I didn't even think of that.
That said, I get the feeling Okinu is just using me to her advantage.
But yes, this is a good opportunity to get our hands on NPP's weakness.
Oryo!
Oryo-sama!
Oh my Oyuki,
did you get transferred to the Okinawa Police Station
because you became useless in the Metropolitan Police Department's Security Division?
Unfortunately not.
The Superintendent General has been invited to an informal conference, hosted here next month.
I'm here for the preliminary planning session.
Chairman Tadomura and the Superintendent General?
Yes, it was originally planned to have NPP handle VIP bodyguard duties.
I'm sorry, Oryo-sama.
To be honest, I would have liked to use your family business, JACES, but...
Dirty money's been used, right?
To be here for a preliminary planning session for something like that...
The job's perfect for you since you like illegal things.
Who did you say likes illegal things?
You're far more knowledgeable about underground matters.
Now, now.
And?  Why are you here on this island, Oryo-sama?
I hope you don't intend to bring harm to Chairman Tadomura.
Visiting.
Lies.
Izumida-kun, let's go.
So basically, it's a battle for market share between two companies that make up 80% of Japan's security industry:
Yakushiji's JACES and Tadomura's Japanese Private Police.
I told you that I'm just visiting.
Didn't you come here to investigate the chairman of NPP, which is growing its share?
What if I told you that they went out of their way to build a villa in the environmentally valuable mangrove forest
and that numerous environmentalists have gone missing there?
Is that true?
Anyway, why don't you take a swim?
I'll go stay at some guest house.
To be honest, resort hotels like this don't suit me.
The environment here is beautiful, yet they build such artificial and unnatural buildings.
Appreciate the environment in a comfortable room that's air-conditioned and clean.
Isn't this the sight of man winning against nature?
Um, I've brought champagne.
You're...!
Hey, you!
W-Why are you running away?
For before...
Thank you.
No, it's okay.
I'm embarrassed.
I take part in environmental conservation activities,
yet I work part-time for a place that arose from nature's destruction.
I heard your comrades have gone missing at Tadomura's villa.
You know about my father?
Your father did?
Yes.
We have no proof.
The police decided that he just ran away.
But there's no way my father and the others would abandon this island and leave.
He was supposed to have gone to the villa to negotiate that day too.
Father, eh?
What good can come from eliminating mere environmentalists?
To NPP, the organization the police approached, it would have been...
What's this?
How uncommon.
I think it's a kyouzuka.
[Note: A kyouzuka is a stone with something scriptural written on it.]
There are legends of a monk from Kouya who was cast ashore from Fudarakutokai.
Superintendent.
Yes.
And it is said that he planted stones with scripture written on them in the streets.
He sealed away the monsters and dragons that made people suffer.
The actual stones have been unearthed from that time.
Okinawa deserves such legends.
It is said that a spirit, by the name of Kijimuna, lives in the mangrove.
I don't know if it really exists.
But there are times when nature itself feels like God.
That's why...
Nature is God.
That is why you want to protect it.
The person who appeared at Tadomura's villa
is a highly-ranked officer of the
Metropolitan Police Department.
Even if the city police have been bought out, if you ask her directly,
reopening the case for the missing people might be possible.
That woman has a strong sense of justice.
The Chairman will see you now.
Thank goodness.
I heard he wasn't too well, so I was worried.
This  is a courtyard?
It's huge.
Yes, it is.
What?!
Wh-Wh-What are those?
The mangrove's vivipary seeds!
Warning.
This is private property.
There's someone from the Metropolitan Police Department here.
Warning.
We want her to listen to our story!
This is private property.
Warning.
Is this why you told them about Superintendent Muromachi?
What are you talking about?
But, thanks to them, it looks like we won't be questioned now, even if we sneak in.
Izumida-kun.
Your back.
Yes.
What is it?
It's the activists again.
The seed is controlling people!
Then will we become like them?
Now!
Oryo-sama!
Oryo!  Do you have permission to carry around a gun?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing, Izumida-kun?
Oyuki, I could save you if you beg.
You've got to be kidding me!
Geez.
The saving comes after she begs!
It's grotesque.
I wonder if this is Kijimuna.
It's probably a mutant species of mangrove.
The other security guards are controlled by this thing too.
We need to remove them.
I'll leave that to you two.
Let's go, Izumida-kun.
Y-Yes.
Um, Superintendent Muromachi,
the local citizens are arguing with the security guards at the main gate.
Please go save them.
A-Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
I'm the only one who made it inside.
Where is the lady from the Metropolitan Police Department?
What do you think?
That's a mangrove too, right?
Impossible.
Mangroves only grow in salinized swamps.
They can't possibly sprout inside a building.
Tadomura Ryoujun.
It looks like Tadomura wasn't destroying nature.  Rather, he was expanding the mangrove forest.
This isn't Tadomura's will.
It's probably the vivipary seed's doing, the one stuck in him.
This can't be.
At first, NPP may have done genetic experiments to the mangrove.
Either way, a mangrove parasitic on humans was born one day.
While killing off the nuisance, the mangrove used Tadomura's mouth and started its move.
So it can thrive.
Father.
Father!
It expands salinized swamp suitable for vegetation.
Changing the environment to be hospitable to itself isn't just humanity's specialty.
It'll make this whole island a swamp soon.
Superintendent!
If God is someone with the power to change the world to his liking,
these monsters would fit that definition perfectly.
Izumida-kun, give me your gun.
But I don't have one on me.
A stone that seals away monsters, eh?
Superintendent, let's run for it.
We're running away.
Take that!  Take that!
Assistant Inspector Izumida!
Oryo-sama!  Thank goodness you're safe.
Target acquired.
The napalm is ready.
Did I just hear something about napalm?
Napalm?
We're going to burn it down.
The entire forest.
I don't intend to get permission for it.
Thank you for always taking care of my little sister.
Okinu!
Yes, I am Yakushiji Kinuko.
It's been 29 years since I was born as the family's eldest daughter.
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File,
File Number 08:
Tamagawa Suicide.
Please look forward to it.
And with fallen leaves, I almost...