Entering the
Capital Freeway.
No delays yet.
We should arrive at
Fukui in five hours.
Hey, aren’t you loading
a little too much?
Keep your distance
just in case.
I know.
That bastard!
Wait!
We have to get
out of here first.
Fifth File
The Bug that Crawls the Omotesando
My name is
Izumida Jun’ichirou.
I am Yakushiji Ryouko’s butler…
… or so it seems.
For some odd reason, it seems my master loves to get involved in my private affairs.
Umm, Superintendent, do you actually have something to tell me?
You’re misunderstanding something.
I just happened to come this way and it was just coincidental that I sat here.
And it’ll be terrible
if something happens…
Meeting with a grade
schooler here so late…
Nothing will happen at all!
Besides, I’ve already told you that Mana-chan is my cousin.
Even if she’s your cousin,
it’s still a crime.
Say, Mana-chan,
why don’t you tell me?
Your mom was really worried that you might be bullied at school.
You promised your mom
that you’d tell me, right?
She doesn’t want to tell you.
Why don’t you leave her alone?
Superintendent!
Being bullied
isn’t that simple.
Even though you say that, you actually just want to talk to grade school girls, right?
Hey!
Jun-chan, you’re the one
who broke your promise first!
Jun-chan?
What do you mean?
I told her that I would
tell you if we were alone.
Why did you bring
this woman with you?
“Bring” and “tagged along” are two totally different things, but…
I’m sorry.
I apologize for that.
So would you please
tell me the truth?
Fine.
Great.
I’m not actually being bullied.
I had a fight with a friend and my mom just overreacted.
Really?
Then you should have
said so in the beginning.
But you’d have left
right away if I did.
Say, Jun-chan.
Who is she? She has
nothing to do with this.
What a rude thing to say!
I’m Izumida-kun’s ruler.
Ruler?
She’s my boss,
Superintendent Yakushiji.
Superintendent?
Superintendents are really
powerful people, right?
Isn’t she younger than you?
Or is she unexpectedly old?
Old?
She’s a career bureaucrat.
Career?
Oh, I know about them.
They’re people who don’t do much work but they boss others around. They’re egocentric.
I believe most career bureaucrats are great people who shoulder Japan’s future.
However, she’s definitely correct about Yakushiji Ryouko’s selfishness.
Well then, the case
is closed, right?
Kids should go home.
She’s right.
It’s already very late.
Mana-chan,
I’ll take you home.
As ordered, we’re at
Aoyama Broadway.
Yes.
Roger.
Transporters, I don’t think you can make it to Fukui after all.
Another truck
will be here soon.
We’d like to transfer
the material.
The door’s bent.
I think it’ll be faster
if we dismantle it.
I’ll leave that to you.
Please hurry.
Yeah, we’ll start right away.
They brought the truck to a building we guard just to transfer the material.
It must be something they really don’t want anyone to know about.
Lower the shutters
at the entrance!
Don’t let that thing out!
It started to move.
We can’t do anything
about it on our own.
Please send
reinforcements at once!
Reinforcements. Hurry!
But why did you fight
with your friends?
It’s because they
said stupid things
after looking at my
photographs without telling me.
Photographs?
Photographs of what?
It’s… I forget.
They were just
ordinary photographs.
I heard gunfire.
It came from that building!
Superintendent!
Hey, Jun-chan,
where are you going?!
Superintendent!
Inside this building?
Jun-chan!
How could you
leave me there?!
Oh, I’m sorry.
This is Aoyama Broadway, right?
What do you want?
The store has already closed.
Did you really hear gunfire
coming from this building?
What are you doing?
Can’t you tell?
I’m sorry, Mana-chan.
Can you go back to the
store and wait there?
What about you, Jun-chan?
I can’t let her go alone.
I’ll be going in too.
Can you?
Of course I can.
Good girl.
Jun’ichirou, you idiot.
Superintendent,
where are you?
Over here, Izumida-kun.
Really…
Does he think he can
just leave me alone?
They’re already dead.
All of them.
How awful.
It looks like they’ve been
cut up with a knife.
A very sharp one at that.
Huh? If a knife was the weapon,
why was there gunfire?
It was probably theirs.
A gun!
Why do they have guns?
It means that they’re not
ordinary transporters.
This is the uniform of the
Japanese Private Police.
The Japanese Private Police?
That’s the biggest rival of JACES,
your father’s company.
Things are becoming fishy.
What do you mean?
It looks like the one that killed
the security guards is still in here.
We don’t even know who he is.
It’s dangerous in this darkness.
Yes, this isn’t a fun situation.
Let’s retreat for now.
You see the
elevator up ahead?
I understand. Let’s go.
Jun-chan!
Jun-chan, where are you?
Mana!
Don’t come, Mana!
Go back!
Jun-chan!
Mana! Mana!
Calm down, Izumida-kun.
It’s all my fault.
I shouldn’t have
left her alone.
Wh-What is this?
Don’t talk.
Just get off.
There’s a child down there.
We must go back
right away! She’s in danger!
Shut up!
Who the hell are you?
I’m with the police!
We don’t want to
do anything rough.
After all, we don’t want
any more casualties.
Will you obey our orders?
It’s true.
Listen to me.
There’s a girl that’s still in the underground parking lot.
She’s ten years old.
Shut up!
You guys know what’s
down there, don’t you?
Then please go
save Mana right away.
Hey.
Or else untie me, quickly!
What are you doing?
Hey, bastard!
How is it?
We’ve found it.
But there’s a child
right next to it.
Positive?
Positive.
It’s a girl.
It moved.
The girl’s in danger.
We’ll take her
into our protection.
What should we do?
I can’t see the girl.
We might hit her if we shoot.
She’ll be killed if we don’t
do anything about it.
We must move it
away from her.
But how?
Damn!
What’s wrong?
What happened?
Answer me!
We’ll go down now
and protect the girl.
We are confirming
your identities.
If we find that you’re really from the Metropolitan Police Department, we’ll release you right away.
Stay quiet until we do.
If you use the underground network of the Japanese Private Police,
I doubt the confirmation
would even take a minute.
I don’t understand
what you’re saying.
You intend to buy more time and erase all the evidence, right?
The corpses and
that killing machine.
I don’t know who you are,
but I think it’s best for both of us if you
don’t stick your nose where it doesn’t belong.
Keep an eye on them.
Yes, Sir!
The rest, come with me.
I’m sure she’s fine.
That’s if my
assumption is correct.
Rather, the ones in danger are the Japanese Private Police.
They’re a security company.
Yet, they enter wars and replace the military in war-torn regions behind the scene.
They’re a dark organization.
The soldiers are
probably from there too.
We’re in the control room.
We can switch the basement
to backup power any time now.
Okay, switch it.
Roger that.
No, Izumida-kun!
Not here! No!
Someone save me!
What’s wrong?!
What do you
think you’re doing?
No!
You can’t! Izumida-kun!
Pervert!
Superintendent,
that’s enough.
Is it already over?
How boring.
We’re not playing around.
We’ve found it.
It’s at the end of the west block,
in front of the wall.
Got it.
Everyone move
to the west block.
It seems like the machine moved to the west of the parking lot.
Let’s go too.
You should leave the gun.
But…
You know what that
machine is, don’t you?
Probably.
The Japanese Private Police were recently given complete control over the protection of nuclear power plants.
The decisive factor was the completely autonomous security robot they had secretly invented.
Why do you have such intimate knowledge about your rivals?
It’s only natural.
They probably got into an accident during the transfer or something like that.
They evacuated it to this building guarded by the Japanese Private Police.
But the robot malfunctioned due to the shock of the accident and went berserk.
That’s probably
what happened.
It seems like it
has already started.
That’s terrible.
That thing wasn’t
built just for security.
Exactly.
That isn’t just
a security robot.
Bastards, why are you here?
How does it feel to be chased around by the anti-terrorist weapon you invented?
Wh-What do you mean?
You armed it so that it would be able to defend against terrorist attacks on a nuclear power plant.
An anti-terrorist weapon.
That’s what it is, right?
Are you saying the government approved of something like that?
Of course not.
That’s why they’re
desperately hiding it.
But too bad.
I just called them earlier, so it’s only a matter of time before the police arrive.
I warned you about sticking your nose
in places where it doesn’t belong.
Izumida-kun, you too.
What?
Y-Yes.
Why?
Even if it malfunctioned,
it didn’t go completely berserk.
Its ability to distinguish between terrorist and civilian is active.
It decides that by seeing
whether we’re armed or not.
That simple?
The program was running
because it was that simple.
Remember when we were
attacked the first time?
It didn’t attack us
until I took out my gun.
Oh, yes!
That’s when it hit me.
More importantly,
where is she?
Where is Mana?
That centipede probably has a program to evacuate the workers to a safe place when a battle begins.
Mana!
Jun-chan.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I’m sorry.
I… I’m sorry.
No, it’s my fault
for leaving you alone.
I’m sorry.
Jun-chan!
Well then.
Where are you going?
We can’t leave
that centipede be.
Please stop!
It’s dangerous!
I’ll be fine.
Now, centipede,
come get me.
Superintendent!
It stopped.
An eye that distinguishes between terrorist and civilian.
After losing that, it may harm
a civilian when it blindly attacks.
For safety’s sake, an emergency shutdown is the only thing it can do.
That is also a basic program.
That robot was trying
to protect me, right?
Yes, I guess it was.
Why does she have
a smile on her face?
I have a bad
feeling about this.
Now the Japanese Private Police won’t be able to protect nuclear power plants.
Don’t tell me that was your
plan from the beginning?
Izumida-kun, the police inspector said he wanted to hear about the situation.
Go.
I’ll look after Mana-chan.
I-Is that so?
Then I’ll go talk to him.
I’ll be right back.
Thank you.
Jun-chan told me
that you saved me.
In truth, I didn’t
actually “save” you.
So, what kind of
photographs were they?
The photographs that caused the fight with your friends were of Izumida-kun, right?
Your friends saw them and teased you about liking older men, right?
How can you tell?
Just tell me.
I’ll give that to you.
As appreciation for saving me.
I don’t want to be
indebted to my rival.
Then I’ll keep it.
Is it really okay for me
to not take her home?
It’s fine.
She’s more mature
than you think.
Besides, you have to
take me home.
It’s already late, so you can stay at my place if you want to.
Are we going to marathon “Mystery, Thursday the Twelfth” until morning again?
Before we do that, you must give me a massage, because I’m tired.
That’ll make me
a manservant!
No way!
It’s an honorable job,
unworthy of you.
The people and events in this work are purely fictional.
Any resemblance to existing people or events is entirely coincidental.
Chizumiru Indajuu.
What’s that?
I’ve rearranged your name,
Izumida Jun’ichirou.
And that would make me—
Yakushiji Ryouko’s Supernatural Case File,
File Number 06: Maid in Kasumigaseki.
Please look forward to it.
Jiryo Yakujiko—