[Note: This is a poem by Saigyou Houshi.]
I wish to die in spring, under the blossoming trees,
on full moon's day during the month of February.
Dubois?
The Metropolitan Police Department?
What business does the Paris district police department's perverted vice-chief of bureau have with me?
So that woman's... started to make her move.
Izumida-kun.
S-Superintendent!
I thought you were dead!
Yes, I am, but...
Wait!
Please stop!
Let us bid farewell to the pair making their way to God's side.
Farewell, you two.
Both of you, may your days be filled with happiness.
Make sure you rest in peace.
Senpai, you can leave the rest to me.
Wait a second!
Keep a close eye on her so she won't come back to haunt us.
This can't be!
W-Wait! Hey!
Wait!
Even Hell would feel like Heaven if I'm with you.
No, if you're with me, even Heaven will feel like Hell.
That was a nightmare.
I remember dreaming the same dream about two months ago.
Just like back then...
What unpleasant mornings.
But what awaited me at the Metropolitan Police
Department was completely different from a nightmare.
It was unexpectedly good news.
Okay!
What do you mean?
As I said, we received a call from Superintendent Yakushiji earlier.
Apparently, she won't be coming here for a while.
It sounded like she was calling from the airport.
Airport?
She probably went out of the country for a vacation.
Probably.
I see.
I know!
It's not like we're doing this behind her back or anything, but do you guys want to go for a drink tonight?
Sounds good!
In that case, there's a Cantonese
restaurant that I'd like to recommend.
Cantonese food, huh?
I'm not too fond of oily food.
Izumida-san, good morning.
Oh, good morning.
When you get older, the oil feels heavy in your stomach.
I see.
I have a message for you.
Tonight, I think we should go somewhere cheap and light.
Okay, I've given it to you.
How about it?
Yes, that sounds good too.
I see.
Leave the restaurant to me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh my, thank you!
Lieutenant Izumida?!
I'm very sorry.
Yakushiji makes me do this every time, so I just...
Those actions are unworthy of a public servant.
I agree.
Refrain from such actions in the future.
I will keep that in mind.
But since I've already brought it along, please use it.
Just this once, as an exception.
Coming here an hour earlier than your appointment.
Was that Oryo's teaching too?
Something like that.
But thanks to that, I...
Hm?
Oh, it's nothing.
I almost said, "My eyes were treated to a feast."
Do you remember this place?
Yes.
If I remember correctly, during the Tokyo Nightmare case...
Huh?
No, nothing.
What do you mean by the Tokyo something or other?
Umm...
Actually, recently she has been giving
names to the cases she's been involved in.
She's still a genius when it comes to thinking up strange things.
Regarding her...
I hear she's out of the country right now.
So you knew.
Yes, my boss's whims are troublesome.
And?
Did you want to discuss it?
Do you know this woman?
No, I don't.
I see.
How about Oryo?
I wouldn't know unless we asked her.
Yes, I would think so.
Who is she?
Most likely the Queen of Shiba.
Shiba... you mean that Shiba?
Shiba refers to the Metropolitan Police
Department's government office tower in Shiba.
Ultra-secret departments, even those among the
Metropolitan Police Department, have offices there.
It's a place even Yakushiji can't touch very easily.
Superintendent Muromachi had a passing relationship
with a man formerly stationed there, a man named Hyoudou.
And that's why she's been secretly observing Shiba on her own time.
I finally understood why Superintendent Muromachi used JACES Sports,
a place practically owned by her archenemy, my boss.
Investigations of the Shiba tower
would be partly taboo for someone working for the Metropolitan Police Department.
Our conversation would never leak outside if it happened here.
Apparently, Shiba is controlled by a
mysterious woman known as the Queen.
Is that the woman in the picture?
I can't be sure.
But most likely.
I was hoping you might have some information.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
There's no need for you to apologize.
This isn't police work.
This is something I am doing personally.
Superintendent, do you plan to keep investigating Shiba?
Yes.
In that case, although I know my place, let me say one thing:
Shiba's influence is enormous.
I know.
That is why I ask that you treat your investigation with the utmost care.
I'll keep that in mind.
But you won't tell me to stop, will you?
Yes.
I know how to state my opinions to a stubborn superior.
Are you saying that I'm as stubborn as Oryo?
Lieutenant Izumida!
That perception of yours is wrong!
I'm terribly sorry.
Correct it at once!
It was an inappropriate remark!
Oh no, my mouth slipped at the very last moment.
Man... I wonder when this'll end.
Oh yeah, I need to stop by the Yodozakura Hobby Museum.
Yakushiji Ryoko knows all your secrets, right?
With the thought of removing Yakushiji Ryoko,
I've initiated a certain plan, for your future...
No, for the future of this country.
First, there will be a big shift in the world of politics.
The beer tastes awfully good today.
It does.
Delicious!
Izumida-san, you're getting too carried away.
It's been a while since I've come to a place like this,
since I used to always escort the superintendent.
I don't know if I should pity you.
Next is politics.
The opposition party that strongly condemns bureaucratic amakudari has,
as of this national assembly...
I would think that this is causing a fuss with the higher-ups.
Being non-career bureaucrats, it doesn't concern us... or rather, that is what I'd like to say,
but that's not the case for Superintendent Yakushiji.
What do you mean?
Why do you think that Superintendent Yakushiji has so much power?
It's because she's strong, beautiful and her personality resembles that of a devil.
Well there's that too, but that's not all.
About 90% of the Metropolitan
Police Department's bureaucrats
go amakudari to JACES or one of its
associated companies after they retire, right?
I see!
If they go up against Superintendent, they'll lose their jobs when they retire.
That's how it is.
It's because of this amakudari "bait" that Yakushiji Ryoko can do whatever she wants.
If this bill is passed and amakudari itself is forbidden, then...
Superintendent Yakushiji will be in a pinch!
But it probably won't.
Why's that?
They're just the opposition party.
They'll probably just make a big fuss, but in the end, nothing will happen.
Although it's a different story if the country accepts all of the opposition party's bills.
It probably won't happen and...
Here are your servings of Yakitori!
They're here!
For seconds, can I have Shochu with coarse tea?
Oh, me too.
I'll get a double Baigor.
Two coarse teas and a Baibai.
Understood!
But one week later, the impossible happened.
Is Yakushiji Ryoko currently following up on the news that would endanger her position?
Oh, what time is it right now?
My head hurts.
I drank too much last night.
On to the next topic:
"The root of all evil is the beautiful, female superintendent.
Her name is Yakushiji Ryoko."
What?!
This is from Nitto Sports's city news section.
In relation to the Metropolitan Police Department's amakudari problem,
most people are interested in the most prominent amakudari destination
and Yakushiji Ryoko, the woman next-in-line at JACES.
She's an elite police bureaucrat who graduated from Tokyo University.
She's beautiful, cunning, and her father is a former Metropolitan Police Department bureaucrat.
A thoroughbred.
The article also states that, on the other hand,
her selfishness is also well-known within the Metropolitan Police Department.
They wrote an article on Oryo-chan?
It also states that, according to witnesses,
Superintendent Yakushiji's selfishness was incomparable.
I don't want to hear anything bad about Oryo-chan!
She thinks that the police organizations that exist for the country's safety belong to her.
Letting a woman with no respect for the country
whatsoever stay in the Metropolitan Police Department is
very dangerous, even if she's in management.
Besides, around us are...
There have been numerous bureaucratic scandals in the past,
so I don't believe the citizens will be content until she provides an explanation.
And the government's response is nothing but poor.
What is this?
Why is every channel broadcasting something about Oryo-chan?
Things have become troublesome.
We've decided to write a special article on Superintendent Yakushiji too.
Even Nitto Daily?
Not just us.
Everyone who visits the Press Club.
What?
How about it, Izumida-han?
Want to be my personal informant?
No.
I'll pay.
It's for helping me with the coverage.
Putting aside whether Yakushiji is right or wrong,
it's vexing that you think I'm
someone who would sell out his boss.
That's great.
But if you don't treat the situation accordingly,
you'll end up falling ill due to being
bashed 24/7, like some prime minister.
It's great that you care for your boss, but be careful not to end up in the same coffin.
Well, I'll be on my way.
Oryo is all over the place.
I'm sorry for all the commotion.
There's no need for you to apologize.
It's Oryo who needs to.
But why did it turn out like this all of a sudden?
Regarding that.
Shiba has made its move, it seems.
Apparently, they leaked information about Oryo to the media.
Really?
But what's their motive?
They might have thought that
the closing of the amakudari loophole
was an opportune moment to crush Yakushiji Ryoko.
"Serves her right,"
is what I'd like to say, but we can't say that in a very nice way.
If they're going to crush Oryo,
they should lower the iron hammer in the name of the law, fair and square.
Not by using the media.
Superintendent Muromachi, they just keep on coming.
We need more guards.
Oh, Senpai!
You came at the right time!
You're the one who came to me.
Please hold a press meeting as Oryo's direct subordinate.
If you do, I'm sure everyone will be content and leave.
Wait!
No, I can't hold a press conference...
You just need to say a few words.
Now, now.
Lieutenant Kishimoto!
It's Lieutenant Izumida!
Excuse me!
W-Wait!
Please tell us!
Where is Yakushiji Ryoko right now?
Is it true that she fled?
What is your relation with her?
Please answer!
Make way!
Umm...
Get in!
Yes!
Thanks for saving me.
Her expression was unquestionably different from ten days ago.
Could it be due to the Amakudari Regulation Bill and the stinging broadcasts?
No, she's looking at something... completely different.
That is what I felt.
Yours.
Why are you giving me something like this?
It's to protect yourself.
Please take it.
What do you mean?
You'll know when we get there.
Where are we headed?
And take this too.
This is...?
It's a card key I've created using the data
collected from the Japanese Private Police.
With this, all NPP keys are good for nothing.
Why are you giving me something like this?
Like I said...
I'll know when I get there, eh?
This way.
What's wrong?
Shh.
Hide!
That's the security robot for nuclear power plants!
They even have those things...
What exactly is stored here?
Marianne, Lucienne, can you play with the dangerous kid there?
Yes, Mistress, leave it to us!
Wait!
S-Superintendent!
Open it.
Ryoko-san,
it's so like you... to come barging in.
I won't let you have your way, Queen of Shiba.
Isurugi Ruriko.
That's...
Superintendent?
I'm still... alive.
A child?
She looks identical to you!
Why?
Why is she a kid?
What were you like when you were little, Superintendent?
The same as I am now.
Beautiful, pure, kindhearted, completely innocent, and loved by everyone...
Yakushiji Ryoko's Supernatural Case File,
File Number 09-B:
Trap in Azabu.
Please look forward to it.
And umm...